正确的
right
所以我们应该开始一个新主题，不仅适用于
so we're supposed to start a new topic that is not only applicable to
that is not only applicable to probabilistic graphical models but to
概率图形模型，但可以进行任何贝叶斯推断，
probabilistic graphical models but to any sort of Bayesian inference and that
any sort of Bayesian inference and that is with school variational method to
用学校变分法来近似后验分布
is with school variational method to approximate posterior distributions okay
approximate posterior distributions okay and we will do some elementary examples
我们今天将做一些基本的例子，也许一些适用于
and we will do some elementary examples today maybe some applied to
today maybe some applied to probabilistic graphical models and there
概率图形模型，并且该主题存储有很多，也许我们
probabilistic graphical models and there is a lots of this topic store maybe we
is a lots of this topic store maybe we will spend another two lectures or three
还要花两堂课或三堂课，这取决于您的疲惫程度
will spend another two lectures or three lectures depending how exhausted you
lectures depending how exhausted you seem to be you know in the days ahead
好像是你知道在未来的日子里，所以不要睡着吧，好吧，我
seem to be you know in the days ahead so try not to sleep okay all right I
so try not to sleep okay all right I believe Subic sent you the notes but I
相信Subic给您发送了笔记，但是如果您发现任何错误，我会把它们贴出来
believe Subic sent you the notes but I will post them if you find any mistakes
will post them if you find any mistakes on this nas please email me so we're
在这nas上，请给我发电子邮件，以便我们回到标准问题上
on this nas please email me so we're back to the standard problem where we
back to the standard problem where we have some observed data that I denote
有一些我在这里用文字Z表示的观测数据是潜在的
have some observed data that I denote here with text Z are the latent
here with text Z are the latent variables and we want to compute the
变量，我们想计算给定的潜在变量的后验
variables and we want to compute the posterior of the latent variables given
posterior of the latent variables given the data the light came on and it seems
灯光亮起的数据，看来我假设的相机应该是
the data the light came on and it seems the camera I am assuming should be
the camera I am assuming should be working okay it was not exactly when
工作正常，这不是完全应该的，因为它应该是死自然的
working okay it was not exactly when it's supposed to be it was dead natural
it's supposed to be it was dead natural not with a miracle yes thank you guys
不是奇迹，谢谢你们
因此，基本上给出了X贝叶斯规则的G的概率，因此
it's supposed to be it was dead natural not with a miracle yes thank you guys
so so the probability of G of X Bayes rule basically is given like that so the
因此，基本上给出了X贝叶斯规则的G的概率，因此
rule basically is given like that so the most of the machine learning subject
机器学习的大部分学科领域是计算后验
most of the machine learning subject area is to compute this posterior okay
area is to compute this posterior okay now in addition to G you may have all
现在除了G之外，您可能还拥有我们所看到的所有参数
now in addition to G you may have all the parameters the way we have seen up
the parameters the way we have seen up to now but and we will do some examples
到现在为止，但我们将做一些示例，但让我们越过信用MC，
to now but and we will do some examples but let's cross the credit MC so we are
but let's cross the credit MC so we are assuming that this post is not very easy
假设这篇文章不是很容易计算，或者您知道可能不是
assuming that this post is not very easy to compute or you know it's not maybe
to compute or you know it's not maybe even given in any other litical form
甚至以其他任何合法形式给出，也许是计算机代码，并且以某种方式
even given in any other litical form maybe it's a computer code and somehow
maybe it's a computer code and somehow we're gonna try today to discuss
我们今天将尝试讨论方法论广场，我们可以
we're gonna try today to discuss methodology square we can have some
methodology square we can have some approximation of the posterior that they
他们明确没有先生的后验的近似值，因此您可以考虑
approximation of the posterior that they have explicitly not sir so you can think
have explicitly not sir so you can think you know taking a general of course
你当然会接受专制统治，将其近似为高斯一世
you know taking a general of course tyranny approximating it as a Gaussian I
tyranny approximating it as a Gaussian I mean that can be in a simple example
意味着可以举一个简单的例子，也许高斯还不够
mean that can be in a simple example maybe a Gaussian won't be enough
maybe a Gaussian won't be enough we don't be enough because maybe these
我们还不够，因为也许这些非常高的尺寸，以便您可以
we don't be enough because maybe these very high dimensional so that you can
very high dimensional so that you can think this in the examples we did with
认为在我们对图Z所做的示例中，这可能涉及许多变量
think this in the examples we did with graphs Z can involve many variables
graphs Z can involve many variables approximating the Joint Distribution of
将C的联合分布近似为高斯波不是一个好主意
approximating the Joint Distribution of C as a Gaussian wave is not a good idea
C as a Gaussian wave is not a good idea all right
好的
因此，有一些方法可以做到这一点，
C as a Gaussian wave is not a good idea all right
so there are methods of doing this and
所以基本上是用样本近似于后验
so one is basically to approximate the posterior with samples and in some sense
posterior with samples and in some sense we discuss this a little bit in the
我们在上一讲的背景下讨论了一下
we discuss this a little bit in the context of the previous lecture when I
context of the previous lecture when I refer to particle methods basically to
基本上参考粒子方法来计算预测和吸烟
refer to particle methods basically to compute the predictive and the smoking
compute the predictive and the smoking distribution in in state-space models so
分布在状态空间模型中，因此可以在柜台上使用
distribution in in state-space models so this is using on the counter
this is using on the counter attractively right and the method of
吸引人的权利和今天讨论的方法基本上是一个
attractively right and the method of well are discuss today is basically a
well are discuss today is basically a deterministic method in many ways and
许多方面的确定性方法和我们所说的小服务类别
deterministic method in many ways and small service category of what we call
small service category of what we call various turn on the inference so we're
推论的各种转折，所以我们将尝试近似后验
various turn on the inference so we're gonna try to approximate the posterior
gonna try to approximate the posterior with some form that is sort of
具有某种易于计算的形式，并且
with some form that is sort of computational easy to work with and that
computational easy to work with and that prong is going to involve the
叉将涉及因式分解，因此近似
prong is going to involve the factorization so an approximation that
factorization so an approximation that factorizes this in distribution software
在分发软件中将此因素分解为疾病的每个变量，因此
factorizes this in distribution software each of the variables to disease so
each of the variables to disease so let's say if Z is three variables we're
假设Z是三个变量，我们将其近似为Z 1的q1和
let's say if Z is three variables we're going to proximate this as q1 of Z 1 and
going to proximate this as q1 of Z 1 and Q 2 of Z 2 times 2 3 of Z 3 and then try
Z 2的Q 2乘Z 3的2 3，然后尝试说服每个QI
Q 2 of Z 2 times 2 3 of Z 3 and then try to persuade each of this Q I
to persuade each of this Q I distribution we will say that this
分布，我们会说这实际上已经导致了方法论
distribution we will say that this actually leads to methodologies already
actually leads to methodologies already known in statistical mechanics for you
在统计力学中广为人知，因为您基本上在很多方面都知道几个世纪
known in statistical mechanics for you know centuries basically so in many ways
know centuries basically so in many ways these methods are coming directly from
这些方法直接来自于物理学，并且
these methods are coming directly from physics ok and and sort of the
physics ok and and sort of the techniques that they applied for simple
他们将简单推理问题应用于概率论的技巧
techniques that they applied for simple inference problems to probabilistic
inference problems to probabilistic graphical models to deep learning to
图形化模型，可以对所有内容进行深度学习，它们非常强大
graphical models to deep learning to everything to they're very powerful
everything to they're very powerful methods what their approach metrics
方法他们的方法指标是什么近似方法是您得到了什么
methods what their approach metrics approximate method is you get what you
approximate method is you get what you approximated with right so you're not
正确的近似值，所以您对此不太满意
approximated with right so you're not happy with it too much
happy with it too much okay so in some sense this is a good
好吧，从某种意义上说，这是一个很好的活动区域，如果您想
okay so in some sense this is a good active area preserved if you want to
active area preserved if you want to come up with something better following
基本上遵循理性的思想提出更好的东西
come up with something better following basically the ideas of a rational
basically the ideas of a rational inference all right so let's introduce
推断是正确的，所以让我们介绍一些基本问题，以便
inference all right so let's introduce the some of the basic of the problems so
the some of the basic of the problems so we assume we have collected some data x1
我们假设我们已经收集了一些数据x1至xn，我们假设我们已经
we assume we have collected some data x1 to xn we are assuming that we have
to xn we are assuming that we have latent variables Z 1 to Z n so you know
潜在变量Z 1到Z n，所以今年您知道潜在变量的数量
latent variables Z 1 to Z n so you know this year the number of latent variables
this year the number of latent variables is the same as the number of data so you
与数据数量相同，因此您可以在知道问题的地方思考
is the same as the number of data so you can think of a problem where you know
can think of a problem where you know this is you know if this you are talking
这就是你知道的如果说的是高斯混合气的诞生
this is you know if this you are talking let's say birth of a Gaussian mixture
let's say birth of a Gaussian mixture for its extra ZZ that tells you what
其额外的ZZ可以告诉您混合物的成分是什么
for its extra ZZ that tells you what from what component of the mixture this
from what component of the mixture this is coming so we have n data points and
即将到来，所以我们有n个数据点和潜在参数，但后来我们
is coming so we have n data points and and latent parameters but later on we
and latent parameters but later on we can enrich this with static parameters
可以使用静态参数beta来丰富它，但是现在这就是我们所拥有的
can enrich this with static parameters beta but right now this is what we have
beta but right now this is what we have this is how Joint Distribution who have
这就是我们与e / m合作时如何使用联合分配
this is how Joint Distribution who have played with it when we work with the e/m
played with it when we work with the e/m algorithm and we want to approximate the
算法，我们想近似后验和模型证据还可以
algorithm and we want to approximate the posterior and also the model evidence ok
posterior and also the model evidence ok so we're going to denote the
所以我们将近似值表示为qz
so we're going to denote the approximation as qz so this is the exact
approximation as qz so this is the exact posterior and this is the approximation
后验，这是我们要尝试的后验的近似值
posterior and this is the approximation of that posterior we're going to to try
of that posterior we're going to to try to compute we don't used usually in the
给定X正确，我们通常不使用Z的符号Q来计算，所以这是
to compute we don't used usually in the notation Q of Z given X right so this is
notation Q of Z given X right so this is the distribution in Z but remember it's
Z的分布，但请记住，它是后验的近似值
the distribution in Z but remember it's an approximation of a posterior
an approximation of a posterior distribution ok the very fundamental a
分配好，这是我今天必须使用的最基本的问题，
distribution ok the very fundamental a question that I have to use today and
question that I have to use today and you need to remember it because it's
您需要记住它，因为这对于每一次高质量的机器学习都是至关重要的
you need to remember it because it's essential every quality machine learning
essential every quality machine learning is the question that we see there that
是我们在那里看到的问题，它提出了较长的
is the question that we see there that it raised the long of the of the
it raised the long of the of the evidence so this is the likelihood of
证据，所以这是数据的可能性，所以对数长度的对数
evidence so this is the likelihood of the data so the log of the length of the
the data so the log of the length of the data is this lower bound which I will
数据是这个下限，我将很快定义Q的小车功能
data is this lower bound which I will define shortly the trolley function of Q
define shortly the trolley function of Q plus the cool but liberal distance
加上Q和P之间的冷静但自由的距离
plus the cool but liberal distance between Q and P
between Q and P so P is the exact posterior cure is the
因此，P是确切的后路治疗是我们尝试为您建模的近似值
so P is the exact posterior cure is the approximation we try to model you may
approximation we try to model you may say if you know why is this useful well
说出如果您知道这为什么有用的话，您很快就会知道为什么这有用
say if you know why is this useful well you will see shortly why is this useful
you will see shortly why is this useful okay so let me define things the lower
好吧，让我定义下界基本上定义为
okay so let me define things the lower bound is defined basically as the
bound is defined basically as the expectation with respect to the
关于关节对数的分布Q的期望
expectation with respect to the distribution Q of the log of the joint
distribution Q of the log of the joint likelihood divided by Q of Z so this is
可能性除以Z的Q，所以这是您可以说为什么下限的下限
likelihood divided by Q of Z so this is the lower bound you may say why do I
the lower bound you may say why do I call it a lower bound we will see that
称它为下限我们将很快看到与Q之间的KL距离
call it a lower bound we will see that shortly and the KL distance between Q
shortly and the KL distance between Q and P is defined this way so you may
P是这样定义的，因此您可能想记住两者之一
and P is defined this way so you may want to memorize one of the two
want to memorize one of the two definitions with the sign so that you do
带有符号的定义，以便您正确执行此操作，因此，如果您将
definitions with the sign so that you do this properly right so if you put a
this properly right so if you put a minus sign and this is the distance
减号，这是Q和PQ之间的距离，并且
minus sign and this is the distance between Q and P Q will come there and
between Q and P Q will come there and there and this would be the the exact
在那里，这将是它上升的确切分布，如果您
there and this would be the the exact distribution it rise approximate if you
distribution it rise approximate if you want to put the sign in tight and get
想要把标志放紧并摆脱它，基本上，您将拥有
want to put the sign in tight and get rid of it basically you're going to have
rid of it basically you're going to have to reverse the order and have QC devices
通过PLC效果颠倒订单并拥有QC设备
to reverse the order and have QC devices by PLC effects
by PLC effects okay everybody familiar with the KL
好吧，每个熟悉KL分布距离的人都可以
okay everybody familiar with the KL distance of distributions okay it's not
distance of distributions okay it's not a real distance okay
一个真实的距离好吧，这是一个非对称的量，我们将
a real distance okay it is a non-symmetric quantity we will
it is a non-symmetric quantity we will see actually today but if you have the
今天实际看到的，但是如果P和Q之间的距离不等于
see actually today but if you have the distance between P and Q is not equal to
distance between P and Q is not equal to this so this is very important for this
因此，这对于Q到P的距离而不是P到Q的距离非常重要
this so this is very important for this the distance of Q from P not P from Q
the distance of Q from P not P from Q okay
好的，当Q和P分别是
okay this distance is zero when Q and P are
this distance is zero when Q and P are equal it is greater or equal to zero and
等于等于或大于零，并且因为等于或大于零
equal it is greater or equal to zero and because it's greater or equal to zero
because it's greater or equal to zero what you see here is greater or equal to
您在这里看到的是大于或等于2l q
what you see here is greater or equal to 2l q
2l q and that's why we call L Q the lower
这就是为什么我们将LQ称为您选择的对数可能性的下限
and that's why we call L Q the lower bound to the log-likelihood you select
bound to the log-likelihood you select because the KO distance is positive
因为KO距离是正数，所以Q的M是一个下界
because the KO distance is positive right so the M of Q is a lower bound
right so the M of Q is a lower bound basically to the log likelihood so if
基本上是对数似然的，所以如果您真的想近似
basically to the log likelihood so if you want really an approximation of the
you want really an approximation of the log likelihood because this is
对数似然，因为这在计算上是
log likelihood because this is computationally the
computationally the to come thing to do what is very easy to
做一件很容易做的事就是计算机爱你，因为它
to come thing to do what is very easy to do is computer love you because it
do is computer love you because it involves the joining of log magnitude
涉及到对数幅度的连接在这里好吧，我们只在
involves the joining of log magnitude here okay and we only have seen in the
here okay and we only have seen in the contest of expectation maximization in
期望最大化竞赛实际上是您想要的原因
contest of expectation maximization in fact there is a reason you would like to
fact there is a reason you would like to work with the affection Z because for
与情感Z一起工作，因为例如，如果此联合分布为
work with the affection Z because for example if this joint distribution is
example if this joint distribution is Gaussian everything falls nicely and the
高斯一切都很好，计算很容易，但是很有效
Gaussian everything falls nicely and the calculations is easy but working
calculations is easy but working directly with this it requires
直接与此相关，它需要在Z中集成，而这并不是
directly with this it requires integration in Z and that's not
integration in Z and that's not convenient to do let's prove this
方便进行让我们证明这个等式证明是微不足道的
convenient to do let's prove this equation the proof is trivial
equation the proof is trivial so the we use the definition of L of Q
所以我们使用Q的L的定义所以很多Q我们将其定义为
so the we use the definition of L of Q so a lot Q we define it to be like that
so a lot Q we define it to be like that so this is what it is so I'm expanding
所以就是这样，所以我正在扩展X的Z的T的QZ日志加上Z的Q
so this is what it is so I'm expanding our Q Z log of T of Z of X plus Q of Z
our Q Z log of T of Z of X plus Q of Z log of T of X minus Q of Z log of Q of Z
X的T的对数减去Z的Q的对数Z的对数很好现在可以更长的效果了
log of T of X minus Q of Z log of Q of Z all right nice okay now longer effects
all right nice okay now longer effects does not depend on Z so I can put
不依赖于Z，所以我可以放在积分之外，我假设Q
does not depend on Z so I can put outside the integral and I am assuming Q
outside the integral and I am assuming Q the distribution huge normalize so the
分布巨大归一化，所以Q DZ的积分将给我1那么
the distribution huge normalize so the integral of Q DZ will give me 1 so what
integral of Q DZ will give me 1 so what I'm gonna get is from this term I'm
我要从这个学期得到的是对数的可能性，然后我
I'm gonna get is from this term I'm gonna get the log likelihood and then I
gonna get the log likelihood and then I have basically the rest of the terms
基本上有其余的项，这就是ZX的P的Q对数
have basically the rest of the terms which is Q log of P of Z X okay this
which is Q log of P of Z X okay this term comes from here and then minus Q
项来自这里，然后是Q的负Q的对数，所以这是负的
term comes from here and then minus Q log of Q is there so this is minus the
log of Q is there so this is minus the cubot liberal distance this is the log
cubot自由距离，这是证据的对数，因此您可以看到
cubot liberal distance this is the log of the evidence so you can see that the
of the evidence so you can see that the love of the evidence is the lower bound
喜欢证据的是QP的下界加上KL距离
love of the evidence is the lower bound plus the KL distance of QP okay very
plus the KL distance of QP okay very simple derivation is extremely from the
在知道头部之前，简单的推导是从心理方面进行的
simple derivation is extremely from the mental side prior to you know your head
mental side prior to you know your head spinning and you say to many equations
旋转，你说很多方程，你知道
spinning and you say to many equations you know
well you know this is you will see it actually in publications this things
好吧，您知道这是出版物，您会在其中看到它的实际情况。
actually in publications this things used with zero explanation because you
使用零解释，因为您应该知道这没关系，所以您不会
used with zero explanation because you supposed to know it okay so you don't
supposed to know it okay so you don't explain things that you supposed to know
解释你应该知道的事情
explain things that you supposed to know all right
all right so we explain why this is a lower bound
所以我们解释为什么这是一个下界好吗，这就是你的照片
so we explain why this is a lower bound okay and this is the picture sort of you
okay and this is the picture sort of you want to remember like the only thing we
想要记住，就像我们拥有数据时唯一拥有的就是这一证据
want to remember like the only thing we have when we have data is this evidence
have when we have data is this evidence so we're always trying to maximize the
所以我们一直在努力最大化数据的证据，所以无论未知什么
so we're always trying to maximize the evidence of the data so whatever unknown
evidence of the data so whatever unknown parameters we care starts as Z or static
我们关心的参数始于Z或静态参数theta，
parameters we care starts as Z or static parameters theta the only really really
parameters theta the only really really we can in a Bayesian setting we can
我们可以在贝叶斯设置中，我们可以通过最大化来计算未知数
we can in a Bayesian setting we can compute the unknowns is by maximizing
compute the unknowns is by maximizing the evidence okay and we just have seen
证据还可以，我们只是看到证据是两个词，
the evidence okay and we just have seen that the evidence yes two terms the
that the evidence yes two terms the killing of distance between Q and P and
Q和P之间的距离和下限之间的差被杀死，因此您可以认为
killing of distance between Q and P and the lower bound so you can think the
the lower bound so you can think the problem in two ways one is you say I'm
问题有两种，一种是您说我要最大化右下限
problem in two ways one is you say I'm going to maximize the lower bound right
going to maximize the lower bound right if you maximize the lower about and to
如果您将下限最大化并使其基本等于您
if you maximize the lower about and to make it equal to that basically you
make it equal to that basically you minimize the KO distance you bring it to
最小化将其归零的KO距离
minimize the KO distance you bring it to zero
zero or you can directly work with the K of
或者您可以直接使用距离K进行计算
or you can directly work with the K of distance so whatever is computationally
distance so whatever is computationally profitable would be the way to go but as
有利可图的路要走，但正如我们将仅看到的是平凡的玩具一样
profitable would be the way to go but as we will see only for trivial toy
we will see only for trivial toy problems we work with the KL distance
我们使用KL距离时遇到的问题下界是我们必须玩的
problems we work with the KL distance the lower bound is what we have to play
the lower bound is what we have to play with
和
在文学中，取决于您读过的书，您知道-哪个社区
the lower bound is what we have to play with
in the literature depending what book you read you know - what community to
在文学中，取决于您读过的书，您知道-哪个社区
you read you know - what community to discuss things with the terminology for
用术语讨论事物的下界有不同的财政
discuss things with the terminology for the lower bound has different fiscal
the lower bound has different fiscal makes I'm going to give you one of them
让我要在36的背景下给你一个。所以我们说
makes I'm going to give you one of them in the context of 36 so we said the
in the context of 36 so we said the objective is to maximize the lower bound
目标是最大化下限，您可以将其视为最小化-
objective is to maximize the lower bound you can think of this as minimizing -
you can think of this as minimizing - the lower bound so if you calculate -
下界，因此，如果您进行计算-主动插件的下界
the lower bound so if you calculate - the lower bound by the initiative plug
the lower bound by the initiative plug in a - there then you get minus Q over Q
在-中，那么您得到Q之上的负Q，这是分布Q的熵
in a - there then you get minus Q over Q that's the entropy of the distribution Q
that's the entropy of the distribution Q and then you have minus Q log of P of X
然后您得到X和Z的P的负Q对数，这里的第二项
and then you have minus Q log of P of X and Z and the second term here alright
and Z and the second term here alright you can write it as the expectation with
您可以将其写为对Q的期望，即能量函数I
you can write it as the expectation with respect to Q an energy function that I
respect to Q an energy function that I defined here to be minus the log of the
此处定义为减去绘图爱的对数，如联合似然
defined here to be minus the log of the drawing love like the joint likelihood
drawing love like the joint likelihood of X and C so this T here is minus Ln of
X和C的乘积，所以这里的T是X MC的P的负Ln
of X and C so this T here is minus Ln of P of X MC okay so basically what you
P of X MC okay so basically what you have here is you have this average you
这里是你有这个平均值，你知道能量减去这个熵，这个
have here is you have this average you know energy minus this entropy and this
know energy minus this entropy and this is basically what people in in physics
基本上就是物理学中人们所说的亥姆霍兹自由能
is basically what people in in physics called the Helmholtz free energy all
called the Helmholtz free energy all right so the problem really of computing
对，所以计算Q的问题实际上与最小化开尔文相同
right so the problem really of computing Q is the same as minimizing the kelvins
Q is the same as minimizing the kelvins free energy okay and actually you know
自由能量好吧，实际上您知道您可以使用以下定义
free energy okay and actually you know you can play out with the definition of
you can play out with the definition of the energy and you can build the problem
能量，您就可以将问题构建为对其他类型的图像进行成像的形式
the energy and you can build the problem to a form of imaging other sort of
to a form of imaging other sort of Pharisees like the Gibbs energy and the
法利赛人喜欢吉布斯能量，还好，所以您可以立即看到
Pharisees like the Gibbs energy and the like okay so you can immediately see the
like okay so you can immediately see the similarities with with the distal
与远端力学的相似之处
similarities with with the distal mechanics
mechanics all right I have another interpretation
好吧，我有另一种解释，我们真的不需要它，而是
all right I have another interpretation we don't really need it so rather
we don't really need it so rather elementary a distribution a posterior of
基本分配给定X的Z的后验分布，我们想对其进行近似
elementary a distribution a posterior of Z given X and we want approximate it
Z given X and we want approximate it with Q of G so this you know high
加上Q的G，所以您知道高维也有很多
with Q of G so this you know high dimension also have lots of this and
让我们不必担心您实际上知道这些参数不是静态的
let's not worry about that parameter you know well actually these are not static
know well actually these are not static parameters so the way it is written here
参数，所以它在这里写的方式表明如果您接近婴儿，我们可以说
parameters so the way it is written here it says if you approach babies let's say
it says if you approach babies let's say to be a Gaussian and Omega is the mean
成为高斯，欧米加就是高斯的均值和方差
to be a Gaussian and Omega is the mean and the variance of a Gaussian then
and the variance of a Gaussian then effectively you can think of the problem
有效地，您可以想到计算此参数Omega的问题
effectively you can think of the problem of computing this parameter Omega the
of computing this parameter Omega the defining this distribution okay that's
定义这个分布好了，这就是我想要做的所有事情，但是有一个
defining this distribution okay that's all what I wanted to do but there is an
all what I wanted to do but there is an example basically that demonstrates this
这个例子基本上可以说明这一点，然后再介绍食品的一般知识
example basically that demonstrates this before we go to the general of the food
before we go to the general of the food ology so let me show it to you
学，所以让我向您展示这个简单的问题，实际上不是
ology so let me show it to you this simple problem it's really not
this simple problem it's really not variational metal but it demonstrates
变异金属，但它展示了我们将要做什么
variational metal but it demonstrates what exactly we're going to be doing
what exactly we're going to be doing there in a general context so pimples we
在一般情况下那里有粉刺，所以我们有分布，您不知道
there in a general context so pimples we have a distribution that is you know not
have a distribution that is you know not very easy to work with so there is an
非常容易使用，所以那里像高斯一样有指数
very easy to work with so there is an exponential there like a Gaussian but
exponential there like a Gaussian but there is a sigmoid function and the
有一个S形函数，假设分布是这个还可以
there is a sigmoid function and the distribution of suppose is this one okay
distribution of suppose is this one okay it looks like that and you say I want to
它看起来像那样，您说我想让它变幻，现在好吗？
it looks like that and you say I want to fluctuate this with a nauseam okay now
fluctuate this with a nauseam okay now an obvious way to portray this with the
用高斯描述这一点的一种明显方法是使用拉普拉斯表达式
an obvious way to portray this with the Gaussian is using the Laplace expression
Gaussian is using the Laplace expression can use somebody the Miami with the
可以用拉普拉斯近似值在迈阿密使用某人，或者也许我们会
can use somebody the Miami with the Laplace approximation or maybe we'll
Laplace approximation or maybe we'll have a gives it two months in this class
有一个给它两个月的班级，但是我们去年秋天使用它并且发现了它
have a gives it two months in this class but we use it last fall and it is found
but we use it last fall and it is found that the machine learning so and maybe
机器学习如此，也许您可​​以从图片中猜出
that the machine learning so and maybe you can guess from the picture what the
you can guess from the picture what the Laplace approximation is so what's the
拉普拉斯（Laplace）近似是什么，拉普拉斯（Laplace）近似是什么
Laplace approximation is so what's the Laplace approximation
好的，但最终是高斯人，这意味着高斯中心在哪里
okay but eventually it's a Gaussian with what mean where is the Gaussian Center
它以零为中心的实际分布的均值
it's centered on the zero under the mean of the of the actual distribution on the
of the of the actual distribution on the main okay I mean it looks to be zero
主要好吧，我的意思是这里看起来是零，协方差定义为
main okay I mean it looks to be zero here and the covariance is defined using
here and the covariance is defined using what the curvature of the actual
我们应该在此处实际分布的曲率是多少
what the curvature of the actual distribution that we should here on the
distribution that we should here on the main okay so basically this yes did you
主要好吧，所以基本上这是您为泰勒级数展开的
main okay so basically this yes did you do a Taylor series expansion for
do a Taylor series expansion for expected mean and the second order term
期望均值和二阶项，并且有效地得到高斯
expected mean and the second order term and and effectively you get a Gaussian
and and effectively you get a Gaussian center are out the mean with the correct
中心是没有正确温度的平均值，您知道吗？
center are out the mean with the correct temperature that much is you know the
temperature that much is you know the cabbage is defined by the covariance I'm
白菜是由协方差定义的，对不起，考拉的温度
cabbage is defined by the covariance I'm sorry the temperature of the the koala
sorry the temperature of the the koala is defined by the curvature of the
由您现在要近似分布的曲率定义
is defined by the curvature of the distribution you want to approximate now
distribution you want to approximate now if you see is and we will be discussing
如果您看到的是，我们今天将讨论这些想法，实际上是
if you see is and we will be discussing these ideas today is actually a
these ideas today is actually a variation approximation where in an
变化近似，其中从根本上讲，因为这是一个
variation approximation where in an elementary way because this is a
elementary way because this is a distribution in a single variable Z you
分布在单个变量Z中，您可以将变化或解释说成
distribution in a single variable Z you can tell the variation or explanation as
can tell the variation or explanation as one that minimizes the distance between
一个使Q和P之间的距离最小的方法，如果我们认为您是
one that minimizes the distance between Q and P for if we take you to be
Q and P for if we take you to be Gaussian so you want the approachable
高斯，所以你想使平易近分布成为高斯，你说什么
Gaussian so you want the approachable distribution to be Gaussian you say what
distribution to be Gaussian you say what is the Gaussian e mais de que el
是高斯e mais de que el地区，注意到了很大的不同
is the Gaussian e mais de que el districts and noticed a big difference
districts and noticed a big difference you get from the Laplace of rocks which
您是从拉普拉斯的岩石那里得到的，它们之间的差别很大，所以不仅
you get from the Laplace of rocks which significant difference okay so not only
significant difference okay so not only basically there is a difference in the
分布的峰值基本上是不同的
basically there is a difference in the peak of the distribution but also you
peak of the distribution but also you can see the support of the distribution
可以看到发行版的支持与支持有很大的不同
can see the support of the distribution is very much different from the support
is very much different from the support of the Laplace props Meister but you
拉普拉斯道具Meister的故事，但您知道放纵会怎样，所以拉普拉斯
of the Laplace props Meister but you know what indulgence okay so Laplace
know what indulgence okay so Laplace approximation and here is the various
近似值，这是各种方法，这是我认为的情节
approximation and here is the various approaches and this I think the plot on
approaches and this I think the plot on the right shows what is that the
右边显示什么是曲率
the right shows what is that the curvature
好吧，这就是我认为这只是两种分布的温度
okay so this is I think is just the temperature of the two distributions
temperature of the two distributions basically showing if this is the Laplace
基本上显示这是否是您所知道的拉普拉斯近似值
basically showing if this is the Laplace approximation you know this
approximation you know this it matches basically the the curvature
它基本上与精确分布的曲率匹配，这
it matches basically the the curvature of the exact distribution okay and this
of the exact distribution okay and this is this is the variation all I'm
这就是我所有有色皮肤的人的变化吗抱歉
is this is the variation all I'm somebody with color skin oh sorry need
somebody with color skin oh sorry need to okay so this is the polyester
好的，所以这是聚酯的近似值，这是更大的
to okay so this is the polyester approximation again this is a bigger
approximation again this is a bigger problem right it gives you a sense of
正确的问题可以使您了解各种金属的作用
problem right it gives you a sense of what the variational metals will do it
what the variational metals will do it in this case there's no point of forming
在这种情况下，没有必要形成您知道的下界，因为我们仅
in this case there's no point of forming the you know lower bound because we only
the you know lower bound because we only have one variable basically and there's
基本上只有一个变量，不需要加入最小化
have one variable basically and there's no need to go to join the minimization
no need to go to join the minimization of the curve of the distance between two
两个和三个之间的距离的曲线
of the curve of the distance between two and three
所以我站在那儿说这句话，却没有意识到那是几张幻灯片
so I stood there saying this without realizing that it was a few slides down
realizing that it was a few slides down let's take the real problem now and say
现在让我们考虑一个真正的问题，说G是高维的，所以我们需要
let's take the real problem now and say that G is high dimensional so we need to
that G is high dimensional so we need to approximate this so the first thing we
近似这个，所以我们在这些变分方法中要做的第一件事
approximate this so the first thing we do in these variational methods we
do in these variational methods we factorize the distribution Q of Z as a
将Z的分布Q分解为Qi的分布的乘积
factorize the distribution Q of Z as a product of the distributions of Qi so
product of the distributions of Qi so each of the states so so if you think of
每个州，所以如果您想到这一点，就知道您是否有两个变量
each of the states so so if you think of this you know if you have two variables
this you know if you have two variables Q 1 of Z 1 P 2 of Z 2 okay so if somehow
Z 1的Q 1 1 Z 2的P 2好吧，如果您以某种方式使他们想像得到
Q 1 of Z 1 P 2 of Z 2 okay so if somehow your punch made it to them to be imagine
your punch made it to them to be imagine you even have a product of gaussians in
您甚至在每个变量中都有一个高斯积，但这是一个因式分解
you even have a product of gaussians in each variable right but it's a factorize
each variable right but it's a factorize product okay so this is the essential
产品还可以，所以这是开始的必不可少的部分，所以我们
product okay so this is the essential part to start with alright so we're
part to start with alright so we're going to use this limitation this
将使用此限制对Z的定义Q进行逼近，然后
going to use this limitation this approximation on define Q of Z and then
approximation on define Q of Z and then somehow we're going to use the
我们将以某种方式使用下限的最大值进行尝试
somehow we're going to use the maximization of the lower bound to try
maximization of the lower bound to try to compute what is the form of this two
计算这两只眼睛的形式是什么，我们将假设
to compute what is the form of this two eyes and we're going to assume that
eyes and we're going to assume that there are generational about to start
有几代人将要开始，所以我们将像
there are generational about to start with so we will do this as general as
with so we will do this as general as possible and and after that we which
可能，然后我们根据需要准确地进行应用
possible and and after that we which exactly with applications on if we need
exactly with applications on if we need any additional approximations so I can
任何其他近似值，我可以再告诉你
any additional approximations so I can tell you again
tell you again this is nothing new in machine learning
这在机器学习中并不是什么新东西基本上机器学习的人
this is nothing new in machine learning the machine learning people basically
the machine learning people basically stole the idea from statistical
从统计机制和我们将要推导的内容中窃取了这个想法
stole the idea from statistical mechanics and the derivation we will do
mechanics and the derivation we will do basically leads to the classical mean
基本上是从量子力学引出经典的均值场理论
basically leads to the classical mean field theory from quantum mechanics okay
field theory from quantum mechanics okay so there's nothing you and actually
所以你什么也没有，实际上这就是为什么一些非常聪明的人
so there's nothing you and actually that's why a number of very smart
that's why a number of very smart machine learning people especially in
机器学习的人，尤其是在欧洲，实际上他们曾经是前进的人
machine learning people especially in Europe actually they used to be forward
Europe actually they used to be forward physicists who switch to machine
转向机器学习的物理学家，他们可以赚一些钱
physicists who switch to machine learning so they can make some money
learning so they can make some money okay and they are very successful
好吧，他们非常成功，因为他们的直觉得到了回报
okay and they are very successful because their intuition pays off
because their intuition pays off alright if you work just with the
好吧，如果您只与克里斯蒂安妮（Christiane）合作，那么您会错过现实，
alright if you work just with the Christiane's you're missing reality and
Christiane's you're missing reality and these people know what reality is and
这些人知道现实是什么，他们已经取得了一些重大进展
these people know what reality is and they have done some significant advances
they have done some significant advances in this area okay all right so this is
在这个领域好吧，所以这是我们的化，所以我们插入
in this area okay all right so this is our ization all right so we plug in this
our ization all right so we plug in this to learn about and remember the lower
了解并记住下限是对尊重的期望
to learn about and remember the lower bound it was an expectation with respect
bound it was an expectation with respect with you there is Q and inside here we
和你在一起有问号，在这里，我们的联合可能性就更长
with you there is Q and inside here we had the longer the joint likelihood
had the longer the joint likelihood divided by Q which Q was this product of
除以Q，哪个Q是所有这些的乘积，因为我有很长的时间
divided by Q which Q was this product of all of this and because I have a long
all of this and because I have a long the long the product the this product
产品长的时候，这里的产品变成对数的总和
the long the product the this product here becomes summations of the logs okay
here becomes summations of the logs okay you see
你看
实际的米利班德再也没有什么恐惧会影响命令C除以Z的Q了
here becomes summations of the logs okay you see
again the actual Miliband had few longer fear affects command C divided by Q of Z
实际的米利班德再也没有什么恐惧会影响命令C除以Z的Q了
fear affects command C divided by Q of Z cubes is that so you have longer bad so
多维数据集就是这样，您的坏处会更长，所以您可以得到日志的总和，好吧，我们
cubes is that so you have longer bad so you get summation of the logs okay we're
you get summation of the logs okay we're going to try to do is we're going to try
要尝试做的是，我们将尝试估算其时间，其中
going to try to do is we're going to try to approximate its time where
to approximate its time where fertilization one at a time right so to
一次正确施肥一次，以便了解是否可以
fertilization one at a time right so to see if you know if that is possible and
see if you know if that is possible and foremost we have a physical intuition I
最重要的是，我有一个物理直觉，我参加了统计学课程
foremost we have a physical intuition I have taken a course in statistical
have taken a course in statistical mechanics or in quantum mechanics this
力学或量子力学中，这个问题将得到解决
mechanics or in quantum mechanics this problem is going to be sort of solved to
problem is going to be sort of solved to such consistency now what that means is
这样的一致性现在意味着我们要计算每个
such consistency now what that means is we're going to compute each of the
we're going to compute each of the factors that say the factor to j then
对j表示因子的因子，然后将其余因子保留到一些
factors that say the factor to j then keeping the rest of the factors to some
keeping the rest of the factors to some values and then we will then update the
值，然后我们将更新下一个保持不变的因子
values and then we will then update the next factor keeping the rest constant
next factor keeping the rest constant until effectively as we play we iterate
直到有效地发挥作用，我们才会遍历所有因素，而无需进一步更新
until effectively as we play we iterate through the factors no further updates
through the factors no further updates are needed this is what's called
需要这就是所谓的自洽
are needed this is what's called self-consistency
self-consistency the way we saw basically the Threadgill
我们基本上看到Threadgill方程的方式好，所以我要绝缘
the way we saw basically the Threadgill equations okay so i'm going to insulate
equations okay so i'm going to insulate the tactical jet so we're gonna compute
战术喷气机，所以我们要计算一下，我们将尝试最大程度地提高这一点
the tactical jet so we're gonna compute we're going to try to maximize this
we're going to try to maximize this lower bound with respect to QJ okay
关于QJ的下限是我们的目标，因为您知道
lower bound with respect to QJ okay that's our objective because you know
that's our objective because you know it's from my direction here so we want
这是我的指导，所以我们希望在此问题上只进行QJ，所以让我们
it's from my direction here so we want on this thing to have oniy QJ so let's
on this thing to have oniy QJ so let's look at this term when I have done
看完这个词，当我做完樱桃后，就会有一个
look at this term when I have done cherries there is a product of for the
cherries there is a product of for the two eyes so that I did is I put this
两只眼睛让我做的是我将这个产品放在积分中将包括
two eyes so that I did is I put this product inside the integral will include
product inside the integral will include all the terms modes a and then I do the
所有术语模式a然后我将果汁苹果树整合
all the terms modes a and then I do the integration of juice apple tree
integration of juice apple tree nothing first you see that right I have
首先没有什么，你知道对了，我有一个整合
nothing first you see that right I have an integration
an integration disease but now I integrate in overseas
疾病，但现在我整合到海外，但今天，然后整合
disease but now I integrate in overseas but today and then the integrations a
but today and then the integrations a separately so this then you get it like
分开，这样就可以得到正确的结果，基本上是
separately so this then you get it like that right is basically the average of
that right is basically the average of the Journal of likelihood with respect
关于另一个人的住房分布的可能性杂志
the Journal of likelihood with respect to the distribution of home of the other
to the distribution of home of the other variables but J okay all right
变量，但J好的，可以把这个东西放到这里，所以我有一些
variables but J okay all right place this thing coming so I have some
place this thing coming so I have some looking on this there on everything
看着这里，除了J还好
looking on this there on everything except J alright
except J alright everything except J and will you agree
除了J之外的所有东西，你会同意我的意思吗，但是在这里我只会
everything except J and will you agree with me but here I'm only gonna have the
with me but here I'm only gonna have the product of the Q eyes at the Thames a
Q眼对泰晤士河a的乘积，因为资金就是你
product of the Q eyes at the Thames a because the funds are you would be
because the funds are you would be integrated with 0 will give me loud
与0积分会给我很大声，因为那里没有J，ZJ还可以，
integrated with 0 will give me loud because there's no J there ZJ okay and
because there's no J there ZJ okay and then I'm gonna have an expert then when
那我要请一位专家，当我在这里拿到QJ的日志时，
then I'm gonna have an expert then when I pick up here the log of Q J and I'm
I pick up here the log of Q J and I'm going to keep here the longer the QJ
QJ曲线以及所有其他项将保持在此处的时间更长
going to keep here the longer the QJ curve as well all the other terms will
curve as well all the other terms will be degraded to one well as a tory
降级为保守的一口井，因为教会本应归一化
be degraded to one well as a tory because the church shall have normalized
because the church shall have normalized okay
好的
all right
所以我让我将这整个事情称为整个括号，因为
so I am let me call this whole thing this whole parenthesis because is going
this whole parenthesis because is going to be a function of Z J because all the
是ZJ的功能，因为其他所有功能现在都可以集成
to be a function of Z J because all the others this would be integrate now right
others this would be integrate now right some what I call this peak with a care
一些我称之为X逗号CJ的高峰，好吧，我声称这是
some what I call this peak with a care of X comma CJ okay and I'm claiming this
of X comma CJ okay and I'm claiming this longer this the wholly integral okay we
更长的时间，这完全不可或缺的好吧，我们将了解为什么现在不重要
longer this the wholly integral okay we will see why it doesn't matter right now
will see why it doesn't matter right now just the I define this to be log of P P
只是我将其定义为PP曲线的对数，所以这是QJ倍
just the I define this to be log of P P curve alright so this is Q J times that
curve alright so this is Q J times that okay and remember I only want to keep
好吧，请记住，我只想保留ZJ的时间，因为我想做一个
okay and remember I only want to keep the times in Z J because I want to do a
the times in Z J because I want to do a maximization with respect to Q J okay so
关于QJ最大化，所以我唯一看不到的是
maximization with respect to Q J okay so the only thing that I don't see any
the only thing that I don't see any future here do you see linkage a of the
未来在这里，您是否看到第二次的链接a也没有任何内容
future here do you see linkage a of the second time there is nothing there also
second time there is nothing there also we don't really care
我们不在乎我们将其称为常量，然后我们将
we don't really care we call it constant and then we have the
we call it constant and then we have the entropy basically of DJ which is this
DJ的熵基本上可以吗
entropy basically of DJ which is this okay
okay the rest is basically functional
其余的基本上是功能优化，这就是为什么这些动词
the rest is basically functional optimization and that's why these verbs
optimization and that's why these verbs are called variational you're going to
被称为变分，您将不得不采用
are called variational you're going to have to take derivatives of this with
have to take derivatives of this with respect to Q J alright and set this
尊重QJ好，并将其设置为零，但您知道我们可以
respect to Q J alright and set this equal to zero but you know we can
equal to zero but you know we can immediately see also from this is the
马上也可以看到，这是右下限，我们可以看到
immediately see also from this is the lower bound right we can see that
lower bound right we can see that without any calculations actually
没有任何计算，实际上没有任何派生，这件事
without any calculations actually without any derivatives that this thing
without any derivatives that this thing here is minus the cool but liberal
这是我们从此P曲线减去QJ的凉爽但宽松的距离
here is minus the cool but liberal distance of Q J from this P curve we see
distance of Q J from this P curve we see that
那
你还记得这里的距离，没有减号吗
distance of Q J from this P curve we see that
you remember the courtly distance without the minus signs here right it
你还记得这里的距离，没有减号吗
without the minus signs here right it would be the minus the integral of kids
将减去孩子的积分，这是一个/可爱的一个，所以您将得到
would be the minus the integral of kids a this / cute a so you're going to get
a this / cute a so you're going to get there was a madness and this is in the
有一种疯狂，这是分母中的另一种-失踪和
there was a madness and this is in the denominator another - disappearance and
denominator another - disappearance and with this thing we get here - which is
有了这件事，我们到了这里-没关系，所以您可以看到
with this thing we get here - which is this okay so you can see what's the
this okay so you can see what's the optimal solution but maximize what is
最优解，但最大化下界L的QJ是多少
optimal solution but maximize what is the Q J that much lies the lower bound L
the Q J that much lies the lower bound L of Q where we are scum again we do the
Q的问题，我们再次败类，我们一次做了优化，
of Q where we are scum again we do the optimization one time at the time that
optimization one time at the time that the rest of the terms have to be left
剩下的这些术语必须保留下来，这样才是最优的QJ
the rest of the terms have to be left alone okay so that is the optimal QJ we
alone okay so that is the optimal QJ we want to maximize this with the - time we
想要最大程度地利用-我们想最小化KL距离的时间是什么
want to maximize this with the - time we want to minimize the KL distance what's
want to minimize the KL distance what's the minimum Athenian distance
雅典最小距离
你有证据，因为我没有
want to minimize the KL distance what's the minimum Athenian distance
you have an evidence because I haven't
零谢谢
zero thank you
这就是minuend赢得了QJ联动价值的最低公司
that's the minuend wins the minimum company for what values of QJ linkages
company for what values of QJ linkages become equal to what
变得等于照顾好一切，所以好吧好吧
become equal to what take care and so all right all right so
take care and so all right all right so k QJ will become equal to this okay and
Q QJ会等于这个好吧，好吧，让我写下来
k QJ will become equal to this okay and all right and and let me just write down
all right and and let me just write down so we defined us to be this picture to
所以我们将我们定义为这张图片，对不起，小图片对，所以
so we defined us to be this picture to be I'm sorry little picture right so
be I'm sorry little picture right so what I'm writing here the longer picture
我在这里写的是更长的图片，这是我的定义，对，这是
what I'm writing here the longer picture is this is my definition right this is
is this is my definition right this is what they have so when you agree with me
他们有什么，当你同意我的看法时，更长的图景就是
what they have so when you agree with me that the longer picture is the
that the longer picture is the expectation with respect to other
除联合声明外，对其他分布的期望
expectation with respect to other distributions except say of the joint
distributions except say of the joint ability could you say this right it's an
能力你能说对吗，这是对所有孩子的期望
ability could you say this right it's an expectation with respect to all the kids
expectation with respect to all the kids but J all right this is the expectation
但是J好吧，这是您对所有Q的期望
but J all right this is the expectation of you know with respect to all the Q
of you know with respect to all the Q eyes but J okay and you told me that QJ
眼睛，但是J好吧，你告诉我QJ这个最优值等于
eyes but J okay and you told me that QJ this optimal going to becomes equal to
this optimal going to becomes equal to PQ all right come on I'm looking for
PQ好的，来吧，我正在寻找方程式，所以你告诉了什么
PQ all right come on I'm looking for that equation okay so what did you tell
that equation okay so what did you tell me that this is optimal when this
我说，当它等于那个时，这是最优的，这意味着我
me that this is optimal when this becomes equal to that so which means my
becomes equal to that so which means my take the logs the run up to j is equal
取对数，直到j的运行等于p KL的对数，而较低的峰值油为
take the logs the run up to j is equal to log of p KL and lower peak oil was
to log of p KL and lower peak oil was this alright and if I write this if I
好的，如果我写这个，如果我对其进行归一化，这是最佳的
this alright and if I write this if I normalize it this is the optimal
normalize it this is the optimal distribution project project
分配项目项目的项目非常仔细地看好吗
distribution project project look at it very carefully okay all right
look at it very carefully okay all right usually an easier way to remember is
通常更容易记住的方法是这里的方程式还可以
usually an easier way to remember is this equation here okay
this equation here okay rather than this so the reason I should
而不是这个，所以我要说的原因是这些字眼与
rather than this so the reason I should say is these words with respect to the
say is these words with respect to the other this that the longer joint of
除此之外，可能性更长的关节还可以
other this that the longer joint of likelihood okay
likelihood okay now obviously if you take an average
现在很明显，如果您对其他所有提示都取平均值，
now obviously if you take an average with respect to all the other cues right
with respect to all the other cues right you have to iterate this that's why I
您必须对此进行迭代，这就是为什么我说您必须假设这样做
you have to iterate this that's why I said you have to assume this to
said you have to assume this to self-consistency so if you start with
自洽性，因此，如果您从说开始，您可以近似地定义
self-consistency so if you start with say and you approximate you define the
say and you approximate you define the optimal for q1 keeping all the other
保持所有其他提示固定不变，对q1最优，然后对进行最优选择
optimal for q1 keeping all the other cues fixed then you go to optimal of
cues fixed then you go to optimal of people to think you won and the rest are
人们以为你赢了，其余的都固定了，你一直在迭代直到
people to think you won and the rest are fixed and you keep iterating until
fixed and you keep iterating until basically you're happy that they are not
基本上，您很高兴他们不是变化，这就是一致性
basically you're happy that they are not changes that's what's that consistency
changes that's what's that consistency means and now why do they call this the
手段，现在为什么将其称为门肯近似法是什么方法
means and now why do they call this the Menken approximation what is the method
Menken approximation what is the method that makes this to sort of be a mean
这使得它成为主要领域的平均领域，我的意思是你所知道的
that makes this to sort of be a mean field of main field I mean what you know
field of main field I mean what you know you can extrapolate from the research
您可以从研究中推断出主要领域是什么
you can extrapolate from the research what is main main field
期望权，以便您知道要使用此权利来计算此权利
expectation right so to come you know to calculate this right you are using the
calculate this right you are using the expectation of the log likelihood of the
您所在位置的似然对数的对数似然期望
expectation of the log likelihood of the join of likelihood where you are with
join of likelihood where you are with respect to the distributions so this is
关于分布，所以这有点您知道，如果您说有很多
respect to the distributions so this is sort of you know if you say have many
sort of you know if you say have many electrons moving around and you want
电子四处移动，你想要一个单电子问题中的光
electrons moving around and you want light in a question for a one-electron
light in a question for a one-electron you know we are doing the computation in
你知道我们正在以电子的平均速度进行计算，然后
you know we are doing the computation in the average speed of electrons and then
the average speed of electrons and then we get there was a political sort of the
我们得到一个政治问题，在这种情况下，我们得到了一个等式
we get there was a political sort of the question in this case we get an equation
question in this case we get an equation for the distribution through J in the
通过所有其他人的平均分布中通过J的分布
for the distribution through J in the average distribution of the other of all
average distribution of the other of all the other guys all right so that's where
其他人都没事，这就是平均场近似值，是的，所以你
the other guys all right so that's where the mean field approximation yeah so you
the mean field approximation yeah so you can feel for example I mean and we may
可以感觉到例如我的意思，稍后我们可能会看到一个例子
can feel for example I mean and we may see an example later on let's say this
see an example later on let's say this factorized distributions come to be a
在这个期望中，因式分解实际上成为高斯分布
factorized distributions come to be a Gaussian in essence in this expectation
Gaussian in essence in this expectation here you can think possibly that they
在这里您可以认为他们可能会在某些情况下出现
here you can think possibly that they may come up that in certain cases what
may come up that in certain cases what you do is you may have to fix the
您要做的是，可能必须将结果固定为其平均值
you do is you may have to fix the results to their mean values right to
results to their mean values right to their mean values
他们的平均值
我不这样认为我不这样认为
results to their mean values right to their mean values
I don't think so I don't think so
但我可以知道一种情况，即您在此处看到的内容之间存在关联
but I can I know one case that there is a relation between what you see here
a relation between what you see here when you use particle approximations but
当您使用粒子近似但汽车的安装喜欢这个时，
when you use particle approximations but installation of the car love this you
installation of the car love this you know it's very different
知道这是非常不同的好吧，这是非常不同的好吧。
know it's very different okay it's very different okay
现在还记得，所以我们去了所有的时间，直到最后一刻才完成这项工作
now remember so we went we did this right with tick all the late and by the
right with tick all the late and by the most pure of Z and we wrote them as a
最纯净的Z，我们将它们写为增税的产物，您知道我们
most pure of Z and we wrote them as a product of tax rise you know we
product of tax rise you know we factorize the Montero at the time
在Kinnock时将Montero分解为Z 1 Z 2 Z 2之一，以此类推
factorize the Montero at the time Kinnock you one of Z 1 Z 2 Z 2 etc so
Kinnock you one of Z 1 Z 2 Z 2 etc so it's now this mission cubes this serves
现在是这个任务多维数据集，它再次服务您知道分发表
it's now this mission cubes this serves again you know the distribution tables
again you know the distribution tables on the market blanket so in this case
在市场毯子上，因此在这种情况下，例如，当您应用这些
on the market blanket so in this case for example when you apply these
for example when you apply these programs this is the summation Bishop
编程这是主教与市场毯子总和并更新一个
programs this is the summation Bishop with the market blanket and updates one
with the market blanket and updates one variable at the time one distribution at
一次可变，一次分配，其余基本上
variable at the time one distribution at a time keeping the rest basically to
a time keeping the rest basically to convey our okay so this is sort of our
传达我们的同意，所以这是我们的事，您可以了解如何将其应用于
convey our okay so this is sort of our you can see how this may be applied to
you can see how this may be applied to you in the context of classical modules
您在经典模块的背景下
正确的
you can see how this may be applied to you in the context of classical modules
right
因此，让我们对此做一个近似，一个非常简单的示例，然后选择
so let's do an approximation of this okay a very easy example then selects
okay a very easy example then selects the slides contain a lot of details so
幻灯片包含很多细节，所以它们是由我的一位大师写的
the slides contain a lot of details so they were written by one of my master's
they were written by one of my master's students okay who was willing and
学生们愿意并且有能力做所有这些偏离的学生，
students okay who was willing and capable to do all these deviations and
capable to do all these deviations and provide all the computer programs I'm
提供我将要在本次讲座中使用的所有计算机程序，好吧，她
provide all the computer programs I'm going with this lecture okay so what she
going with this lecture okay so what she did is she yeah she started with a
是的，是的，她是从多元高斯开始的，在这种情况下，我们
did is she yeah she started with a multivariate Gaussian in this case we
multivariate Gaussian in this case we have two variables only with this mean
他只有两个变量，意思是平均和安静，他说
have two variables only with this mean and quiet looking like that and he says
and quiet looking like that and he says you know what I am going to use this
你知道我要用这个迷你场近似来近似
you know what I am going to use this mini field approximation to approximate
mini field approximation to approximate this Gaussian over two variables as a
高斯在两个变量上作为高斯在其身体上的乘积更多
this Gaussian over two variables as a product of gaussians over its body more
product of gaussians over its body more separate so it's a vectorized proper
分开，所以它是两个单变量高斯向量的矢量化大小
separate so it's a vectorized proper size of two univariate gaussians okay
size of two univariate gaussians okay you may say let me destroy a bubble to
你可能会说让我销毁泡沫来做到这一点，你知道这很有趣
you may say let me destroy a bubble to do this well you know it's interesting
do this well you know it's interesting right I mean can you actually take you
是的，我是说，您实际上可以让您知道这个人有两个变量吗？
right I mean can you actually take you know this guy's on two variables and
know this guy's on two variables and write is the product of thousands in in
write是每个变量在一维中成千上万的乘积
write is the product of thousands in in one dimension for each of the variables
one dimension for each of the variables and it'll be interesting
会很有趣，所以没有捐款，但实际上这是一个
and it'll be interesting okay so no donation but actually it's a
okay so no donation but actually it's a very good way for you to learn exactly
您可以很好地了解这种变化的正确方式，因此请记住
very good way for you to learn exactly how this variation all right so remember
how this variation all right so remember in space the optimal Q line the normal
在太空中，最佳Q线是正常qrz，因此这意味着最佳
in space the optimal Q line the normal qrz one so this now means optimal it is
qrz one so this now means optimal it is the expectation whatever value was
期望值更高，这里Z 2没有隐藏的身体
the expectation whatever value was higher here Z 2 there is no hidden body
higher here Z 2 there is no hidden body or anything that zone is zip here so
或任何区域都在这里压缩，所以Z的P数，所以我在做的是
or anything that zone is zip here so number P of Z so what I'm doing is I'm
number P of Z so what I'm doing is I'm expanding the love of pure silver by
通过高斯的剪裁扩大了对纯银的喜爱。
expanding the love of pure silver by body of Gaussian all right clipping
body of Gaussian all right clipping anything that doesn't depend on
基本上不依赖Z的任何东西
anything that doesn't depend on basically on on the Z one out of the
basically on on the Z one out of the picture okay because we're in interest
图片还好，因为我们对Z 1的分布感兴趣
picture okay because we're in interest on the distribution of Z 1
无论我们做了什么结果，我们都必须对其进行归一化，以确保这是
whatever result we did we're gonna have to normalize it to be sure that this is
to normalize it to be sure that this is integrates to on so keep that in mind so
集成到上面，因此请记住这一点，以便您扩展此术语
integrates to on so keep that in mind so you expand this write this term
you expand this write this term ultraviolet Gaussian you expand and and
紫外线高斯膨胀，然后必须采取保护措施
ultraviolet Gaussian you expand and and then you have to take its protections
then you have to take its protections with respect to Z 2 so every time that
关于Z 2，因此每次具有C-在哪里-您都可以拥有
with respect to Z 2 so every time that has C - where is it - you can have the
has C - where is it - you can have the expectation of Z 2 respectively - okay
分别期望Z 2-好吧，别无其他，我们该怎么办
expectation of Z 2 respectively - okay there is nothing else and how do we
there is nothing else and how do we extract this distribution from this
从此表达式中提取此分布的最规则是
extract this distribution from this expression what is the most rules that
expression what is the most rules that we have to do this is distribution in g1
我们要做的是在g1中分布我在这里看到g1我看到C 1与u 1
we have to do this is distribution in g1 I see g1 here I see C 1 versus u 1
I see g1 here I see C 1 versus u 1 square so what do we need to do to come
正方形，那么我们需要做些什么才能得出一个很好的表达，这是什么
square so what do we need to do to come up with the a nice expression what's the
up with the a nice expression what's the password
密码
不，我就像说过Foursquare，有人派我去完成广场
up with the a nice expression what's the password
no I'm like I said Foursquare and somebody sent to complete the square I
不，我就像说过Foursquare，有人派我去完成广场
somebody sent to complete the square I and I you know square square I left the
我知道方形广场我离开了广场我要说的是关闭广场
and I you know square square I left the square I was going to say closing the
square I was going to say closing the square or completing the square or you
广场或完成广场，或者您知道什么，所以您基本上必须
square or completing the square or you know whatever so you basically have to
know whatever so you basically have to write this you know the three - some
写这个，你知道三个-先生的意思是对的。矩阵乘以D-Ameen
write this you know the three - some mean right mr. matrix times D - Ameen
mean right mr. matrix times D - Ameen all right so you can get the form of a
好的，这样您就可以得到高斯分布的形式，您必须关闭
all right so you can get the form of a Gaussian distribution you have to close
Gaussian distribution you have to close the square on c1 okay so you can be
c1上的正方形好吧，因此您可能会错过三位一体的阅读，如果
the square on c1 okay so you can be missed in a Trinity of reading and if
missed in a Trinity of reading and if you do this in a trivial way it comes
您以一种简单的方式做到这一点，那就是零的最佳分布
you do this in a trivial way it comes that the optimal distribution for zero
that the optimal distribution for zero is and again the Vice here so you don't
一次又一次的恶习，所以您不必动动手指，月亮就来了
is and again the Vice here so you don't have to move a finger the moon comes to
have to move a finger the moon comes to be what you see here okay and the
就是你在这里看到的好吧，对称的最优​​t2出现了
be what you see here okay and the optimal t2 by symmetry comes to look
optimal t2 by symmetry comes to look like that so I remind you me I am you
那样，所以我提醒你我是你们两个，但他们来了
like that so I remind you me I am you two are the means but they're coming
two are the means but they're coming from the bivariate Gaussian and so if
来自二元高斯，所以如果z1的安全性是
from the bivariate Gaussian and so if security of z1 the means of the
security of z1 the means of the univariate gaussians in the
分解中的单变量高斯，所以有一个
univariate gaussians in the factorization alright so there is an
factorization alright so there is an issue here you can nothing issue it this
问题在这里，你什么都没有问题，这正是我们所讨论的
issue here you can nothing issue it this is exactly what we discussed about
is exactly what we discussed about self-consistency to find kill one of z1
要找到杀死z1之一的自我一致性，您需要知道脂质保留为
self-consistency to find kill one of z1 you need to know lipids to remain as
you need to know lipids to remain as they keep we have z2 and to find you 12
他们让我们拥有z2并找到12 G-您需要知道
they keep we have z2 and to find you 12 G - you need to know what is the mean of
G - you need to know what is the mean of q1 of z1 thanks mate let's say this main
z1的q1，谢谢同伴，假设这个主要元素，您完成了这个步骤，然后您
q1 of z1 thanks mate let's say this main and you complete this and then you
and you complete this and then you complete its meaning you are you planet
完成它的意思，你是你在这里的星球，计算这个，你不能做一个
complete its meaning you are you planet in here calculate this you can't make a
in here calculate this you can't make a new mean of this you plug it in and get
新的意思是您插入它并获得愤怒并感到融合好吧，这是
new mean of this you plug it in and get irate and feel convergence okay it's
irate and feel convergence okay it's actually contact but this problem has
实际联系，但是这个问题我真的很喜欢它是解决问题的方法
actually contact but this problem has I really like it is the fix point
I really like it is the fix point solution okay and so the fix point
解决方案还可以，所以定点解决方案基本上在一天结束时
solution okay and so the fix point solution basically at the end of the day
solution basically at the end of the day gives you the chances of you secure all
让您有机会确保一切正常，所以当您进行迭代时，您可以
gives you the chances of you secure all right so when you iterate this you can
right so when you iterate this you can do it but you know gives the answer okay
做到这一点，但您知道给出的答案还可以，所以q1 z1的平均值实际上是新的
do it but you know gives the answer okay so the mean of q1 z1 is actually new one
so the mean of q1 z1 is actually new one and the you know the precision is lambda
而您知道的精度是lambda 1 1，这里是Precision对
and the you know the precision is lambda 1 1 and here the Precision's love with
1 1 and here the Precision's love with you too and I mean me too alright so
你也是，我的意思是我也很好，所以让我没有时间检查我
you too and I mean me too alright so let's I do not have time to check I'm
let's I do not have time to check I'm gonna post this right but there is a
会发布此权利，但实际上存在有关问题的产品计划
gonna post this right but there is a product on problems actually the plan
product on problems actually the plan and get you the pixels of your seat here
并让您知道座位的像素，所以我将向您展示结果
and get you the pixels of your seat here so I'm gonna show you how the results
so I'm gonna show you how the results look like so this is this is the
看起来像这样，这就是多元的高斯变量
look like so this is this is the multivariate Gaussian that to bivariate
multivariate Gaussian that to bivariate Gaussian P of Z and you try to
Z的高斯P，您尝试用此因式近似
Gaussian P of Z and you try to approximate it with this factorized
approximate it with this factorized variational distribution Q of Z alright
Z的变化分布Q好，所以请注意，所以这就是你
variational distribution Q of Z alright so so notice okay so this is what you
so so notice okay so this is what you get all right so this is the product of
没事，所以这是两个单变量高斯的乘积，您会注意到
get all right so this is the product of two univariate gaussians and you notice
two univariate gaussians and you notice that in in the direction of the maximal
基本上是在Z的P的最大方差方向上
that in in the direction of the maximal variance of P of Z basically your
variance of P of Z basically your underestimate X okay so basically here
低估了X好吧，所以基本上您在这里做得很好，但是您知道自己在
underestimate X okay so basically here you're doing good but you know you're
you're doing good but you know you're missing what's going on in there
缺少那里正在发生的事情，所以这基本上是支持
missing what's going on in there so this is basically the support the
so this is basically the support the solution that you get this multiple path
解决方案，您可以获得比Z的实际P多的路径，因此基本上
solution that you get this multiple path than the actual P of Z so basically your
than the actual P of Z so basically your cube Z is over confident approximation
立方体Z过度逼近过程
cube Z is over confident approximation of the procedure
好吧，替代近似有趣，我们不需要知道这个权利
okay alternative approximate interesting we don't need to know this right
we don't need to know this right basically the same derivation I gave you
基本上与我给您的推导相同，我们在进行优化时会在此处看到
basically the same derivation I gave you I see here when we did the optimization
I see here when we did the optimization problem and crossing the constrain but
问题和克服约束，但分配的未来已规范化，因此
problem and crossing the constrain but the distribution future is normalized so
the distribution future is normalized so if you do absolutely this you get the
如果您绝对做到这一点，那么您会立即获得正确的解决方案，因此
if you do absolutely this you get the right solution right away so there's
right solution right away so there's nothing you really on this think I know
没什么，你真的认为我知道无线实际上是不合时宜的
nothing you really on this think I know actually Wireless came out of sequence
好吧，没关系，让我继续对
okay it doesn't matter so let me continue this approximation of the
continue this approximation of the Gaussian think this is what Winston's
高斯认为这就是温斯顿的，我们现在还可以，所以我们提到了
Gaussian think this is what Winston's we're getting okay so we mentioned that
we're getting okay so we mentioned that maximizing the lower bound right is the
最大化下限右与最小化Cooper剪辑或
maximizing the lower bound right is the same as minimizing the Cooper clip or
same as minimizing the Cooper clip or distance between Q and P so it just to
Q和P之间的距离，所以它只是使事情变得有趣，您知道我们
distance between Q and P so it just to make things interesting you know what we
make things interesting you know what we do here is promote instead of minimizing
在这里做的是促进而不是最小化随之而来的Q和P之间的风险QM
do here is promote instead of minimizing risk QM between Q and P that comes
risk QM between Q and P that comes directly from the is a variation of
如果我们尝试最小化，则直接来自原则的变体
directly from the is a variation of Principles if we try to minimize instead
Principles if we try to minimize instead the distance between P and Q for I can
P和Q之间的距离，因为我记得立方机器人的自由距离是
the distance between P and Q for I can remember the cubot liberal distance is
remember the cubot liberal distance is not symmetric so you know anticipate
不对称，所以您知道这将为您带来相同的结果
not symmetric so you know anticipate that this will give you the same results
that this will give you the same results as this so this is the valuation
因为这就是估值的近似值
as this so this is the valuation approximation this is what were
approximation this is what were discussing in this Q lectures this is
在这个Q讲座中讨论，这不是变化近似
discussing in this Q lectures this is not a variation approximation we
not a variation approximation we minimize the KL distance between P and Q
最小化P和Q之间的KL距离可以有很大的不同，所以这就是
minimize the KL distance between P and Q all right big difference so this is what
all right big difference so this is what you get
你得到，所以K在这里看，所以Q就是全部
you get so K here look at the so the Q is all
so K here look at the so the Q is all over the space this is P of Z so P of Z
在空间上，这是Z的P，所以Z的P是0，所以在立方体中，如果可以的话
over the space this is P of Z so P of Z is 0 there right so in cubes if you can
is 0 there right so in cubes if you can see when you minimize the distance
看看何时最小化P和Q之间的距离适合社区
see when you minimize the distance between P and Q it fits for community
between P and Q it fits for community mass where the section values of P of Z
质量，其中Z的P的截面值很小，所以在我们开始之前
mass where the section values of P of Z are very small okay so before we had
are very small okay so before we had another confident solution that
另一个低估此方差的自信解决方案
another confident solution that underestimates the variance in this
underestimates the variance in this direction here we have a solution has
方向，这里我们有一个解决方案，它具有非常高的支撑力，且非零质量
direction here we have a solution has very high support and non zero mass in
very high support and non zero mass in areas for P of Z is equal to zero
Z的P的面积等于零，因此再次确保写出
areas for P of Z is equal to zero so again be sure to write analytical
so again be sure to write analytical problems you minimizing Cal differences
最小化Cal差异的问题是的，这可以节省多大
problems you minimizing Cal differences yes this to be conserve how big
yes this to be conserve how big differences you get when you memorize Q
当您记住Q和Q时，您得到的差异就是U与P的距离与
differences you get when you memorize Q and Q the distance of U from P versus
and Q the distance of U from P versus the distance of P from Q and you can
P与Q的距离，您实际上可以知道您可以期望
the distance of P from Q and you can actually sort of you know you can expect
actually sort of you know you can expect many of this results right so you know
许多这样的结果是正确的，所以您知道，所以让我们为其中一种情况做
many of this results right so you know so let's do one of these cases just for
so let's do one of these cases just for demonstration so in this case we
演示，因此在这种情况下，我们将Q和P之间的距离最小化
demonstration so in this case we minimize the distance between Q and P
minimize the distance between Q and P and this is what this distance is right
这就是这个距离是正确的，所以让我们考虑实际的区域
and this is what this distance is right so let's consider regions of the actual
so let's consider regions of the actual distribution that P of Z given X is zero
给定X的Z的P为零的分布，所以它的观察者无法
distribution that P of Z given X is zero all right so it's observers cannot what
all right so it's observers cannot what this is insane it's me
这太疯狂了，我很好，这非常重要，我们真的很重要
this is insane it's me okay very big it's really crucial big we
okay very big it's really crucial big we actually are going to member of 50s need
实际上要到50多岁的成员最有可能需要
actually are going to member of 50s need that most probably
that most probably so this is big Lee okay TMZ given X is
所以这个大李好吧TMZ鉴于X好大
so this is big Lee okay TMZ given X is big okay
big okay if you get basically you get an infinite
如果你基本上得到了，那么假设那个立方体Z是什么，你将得到无限的贡献。
if you get basically you get an infinite contribution assuming what that cube Z
contribution assuming what that cube Z is not 0 all right assuming a huge list
不为0可以，假设一个巨大的列表0 7并不意味着在区域中
is not 0 all right assuming a huge list of 0 7 doesn't mean that in regions
of 0 7 doesn't mean that in regions where remember to minimize this distance
记住要最小化此距离
分散的意识以色列，您可能会在这里感到困惑，因此在P
of 0 7 doesn't mean that in regions where remember to minimize this distance
dispersed awareness Israel you can confusion over here so in regions that P
分散的意识以色列，您可能会在这里感到困惑，因此在P
confusion over here so in regions that P of Z is 0 she seems to be what
Z的值为0她似乎是
正确看一下这个表达式，并考虑区域为零的字段
confusion over here so in regions that P of Z is 0 she seems to be what
look at this expression right and considering regions were fields is zero
正确看一下这个表达式，并考虑区域为零的字段
considering regions were fields is zero alright
好吧，避免得到零以上是什么
alright to avoid getting the above zero what is
to avoid getting the above zero what is the only option that will lead to an
唯一会导致距离为20的信封的选项
the only option that will lead to an envelope for the distance of 20
印刷机确实具有唯一的使您不受无限影响的方式是当多维数据集时
the presses do have the only way that you get not infinite is when when cubes
you get not infinite is when when cubes that have become zero and this is what's
变成零，这就是Z的Q的零强迫
that have become zero and this is what's called zero forcing for Q of Z and you
called zero forcing for Q of Z and you can take care P of Z is zero right and
可以照顾到Z的P为零，并且在
can take care P of Z is zero right and curves is supposed to go to zero okay in
curves is supposed to go to zero okay in this case and the discussions of the
这种情况以及您可以阅读的下一张幻灯片的讨论
this case and the discussions of the next slide that you can read you
next slide that you can read you basically get the opposite effectively
基本上有效地得到了相反的结果，而在Z的P为
basically get the opposite effectively what you get in regions where P of Z is
what you get in regions where P of Z is 0 Q has positive master Fisto okay right
0 Q拥有积极的大师费斯托，好吧，相反的效果，你可以看到
0 Q has positive master Fisto okay right the opposite effect you can see the
the opposite effect you can see the actual distribution is a becauseum right
实际分配是一个正当的权利，并认为这意味着支持
actual distribution is a becauseum right and believe this means in the prop swish
and believe this means in the prop swish right that's a kind of an interesting
对，这是一个有趣的问题，所以这是让我看看
right that's a kind of an interesting problem so this is this let me see what
problem so this is this let me see what is the actual distribution so the video
是实际的分配，所以视频我说的是
is the actual distribution so the video I the motion of the you say is the
I the motion of the you say is the mixture of gaussians and we try to
高斯混合，我们尝试计算mm的因式近似
mixture of gaussians and we try to compute factorize approximation of mm
compute factorize approximation of mm factorized
基本上为单变量的因式乘积
factorized product for basically of univariate
product for basically of univariate gaussians okay so with your situation
高斯人好吧，所以从最小化开始
gaussians okay so with your situation starting from the minimization of the
starting from the minimization of the total distance between P and Q again I'm
P和Q之间的总距离我要去的是国民
total distance between P and Q again I'm going to this is nationals
going to this is nationals okay again this okay this is not
再次好吧，这好吧，这不是变分方法没有最大化
okay again this okay this is not variational methods is not maximizing
variational methods is not maximizing the lower bound and but so this is how
下界，但这就是循环的近似值
the lower bound and but so this is how the approximation of loops you get
the approximation of loops you get basically the right approximation here
基本上这里的正确近似是单变量是这个的乘积
basically the right approximation here is is univariate is the product of this
is is univariate is the product of this you know you get basically this Gaussian
你知道你基本上就是这个高斯人，你在这里看到的很好，你知道
you know you get basically this Gaussian what you see here okay and you know it
what you see here okay and you know it basically contains the point of the two
如果你去的话，基本上包含了高斯混合中两种模式的点
basically contains the point of the two modes in the Gaussian mixture if you go
modes in the Gaussian mixture if you go however and you
但是，您却使自己成为了国家级甲基
however and you made you do the very National methyl and
made you do the very National methyl and you approximate the you minimize the
您可以近似地将Q和P之间的距离最小化
you approximate the you minimize the care of distance between Q and P you
care of distance between Q and P you will get either a list or either that so
会得到一个列表或一个列表，所以基本上是变分方法Web
will get either a list or either that so basically the variational method web
basically the variational method web browsers it collapses to all of the
浏览器将其折叠为高斯墨西哥的所有模式，所以
browsers it collapses to all of the modes of the Gaussian Mexico okay so
modes of the Gaussian Mexico okay so this is your standard mode collapse
这是您的标准模式崩溃问题，当然还有Sigma
this is your standard mode collapse problem and of course whether Sigma
problem and of course whether Sigma necrosis I mean is this number it you
坏死我的意思是这个数字，你知道怎么可能给你两个
necrosis I mean is this number it you know how is it possible to give you two
know how is it possible to give you two solutions well you know you start with
很好的解决方案，您知道您从一些与自己有关的事情入手，因此需要一些初始
solutions well you know you start with something about your so for some initial
something about your so for some initial guess here would converge there for
猜这里会聚在那儿，其他东西会聚在那儿
guess here would converge there for something else will converge there now
something else will converge there now if you know the initial basis you can
如果您知道初始基础，则可以立即说出百分之五十
if you know the initial basis you can immediately say fifty percent of the
immediately say fifty percent of the time you may get this and fifty percent
时间可能会得到完成，而百分之五十的时间可能会完成，但是
time you may get this and fifty percent of the time you may get done but to the
of the time you may get done but to the right so this is the you know minimizing
对，所以这是你知道的最小化P和Q之间的距离
right so this is the you know minimizing the distance between P and Q this
the distance between P and Q this corresponds the minimization of Q and P
对应于Q和P的最小值，这是我们的变分技术
corresponds the minimization of Q and P which is our variational techniques
which is our variational techniques discussed today okay if we have time
今天讨论，好吧，如果我们有时间，也许在一两个星期内，我们将讨论
discussed today okay if we have time maybe in a week or two we will discuss
maybe in a week or two we will discuss basically the whole huge set of
基本上，整个方法论都包括期望
basically the whole huge set of methodologies include the expectation
methodologies include the expectation propagation basically does lead to this
传播基本上会导致这种类型的近似，
propagation basically does lead to this type of approximations with which we
type of approximations with which we obscure but the variational methods they
晦涩难懂，但是他们的变分方法有多个丢失的问题
obscure but the variational methods they have this problem with multiple lost
好的
okay
我实际上可以利用这个问题，因为您知道很多
I can utilize this actually this problem with you know well there's a lot of
with you know well there's a lot of things that can be asking it here but
可能会在这里提出问题的东西，但您基本上在这张幻灯片中知道了，
things that can be asking it here but you know in this slide basically and I'm
you know in this slide basically and I'm rubber and walk through it because it's
橡胶，并通过它，因为如果有人给你一个基础，这是基本的
rubber and walk through it because it's elementary if somebody gives you an
elementary if somebody gives you an arbitrary distribution P of X in high
X在高维上的任意分布P并表示找到
arbitrary distribution P of X in high dimensions and says find using
dimensions and says find using variational methods a Gaussian
您知道简单的高斯近似的变分方法
variational methods a Gaussian approximation you know the simple
approximation you know the simple example to demonstrate the difference
示例来说明与拉普拉斯近似的区别，但是您
example to demonstrate the difference from the Laplace approximation but you
from the Laplace approximation but you may wonder is there any action the
可能想知道这个组织有什么行动要多元
may wonder is there any action the organization of this to multivariate
organization of this to multivariate distribution can I get the variation of
分布可以得到高斯表达式的变化吗？
distribution can I get the variation of expression of the Gaussian and it comes
expression of the Gaussian and it comes apart so if you do the algebra and I
分开，所以如果你做代数，我在这里拥有一切，我知道你是否
apart so if you do the algebra and I have everything here and I know if you
have everything here and I know if you are not gonna bother to look at it but
不会去烦恼地看着它，但是有人打扰了它，所以出于
are not gonna bother to look at it but somebody bother to type it so out of
somebody bother to type it so out of respect for him you may want to actually
尊敬他，您可能想真正读一读，因为有
respect for him you may want to actually read it all right because there is
read it all right because there is pretty much to learn you know there is a
几乎可以学到，您知道有一个小技巧，您可以做悬挂技巧
pretty much to learn you know there is a little trick that you do suspender trick
little trick that you do suspender trick in machine learning with with this term
在机器学习中用这个术语在这里，我将不讨论它，因为
in machine learning with with this term here I am NOT going to discuss it since
here I am NOT going to discuss it since you need to take derivatives with
您需要在Sigma中对我进行衍生以找到
you need to take derivatives with respect to me here in Sigma to find the
respect to me here in Sigma to find the optimal Q of X you need to know how to
X的最佳Q，您需要知道如何执行此导数，但这是
optimal Q of X you need to know how to do this derivatives but here's the
do this derivatives but here's the answer the answer comes to be that the
答案答案是变化力比的平均值是
answer the answer comes to be that the mean in the variation force ratio is
mean in the variation force ratio is naturally the expectation of X and the
自然地，对X的期望和暴力实际上就是X的协方差
naturally the expectation of X and the violence is actually the covariance of X
violence is actually the covariance of X okay so Sigma is exactly the covariance
好吧，西格玛就是X的协方差，所以实际上没有因式分解
okay so Sigma is exactly the covariance of X so really there is no factorization
of X so really there is no factorization here right so this is a multivariate
在这里，所以这是一个多元高斯模型，所以如果您想这样做
here right so this is a multivariate Gaussian okay so if you want to do this
Gaussian okay so if you want to do this you can use variational methods this is
您可以使用变分方法这不是结果有很大不同
you can use variational methods this is not the result is very much different
not the result is very much different from the Laplace approximation
与拉普拉斯（Laplace）近似值完全不同
from the Laplace approximation okay very much different
您可以将这种金属归纳为某种不同类型的分布，因为
can you generalize this metal to sort of different type of distributions because
different type of distributions because kill distance you know not typically
杀死距离，你通常不知道这决定了我记得你知道我曾经
kill distance you know not typically decides it I remember you know I once
decides it I remember you know I once upon a time I gave a seminar in a
曾几何时，我在一所英国大学举办了一个研讨会，
upon a time I gave a seminar in a British University and one of my
British University and one of my colleagues decided you know it's very
同事们认为您知道这很糟糕，距离也不是很远，因为
colleagues decided you know it's very bad and not a good distance and since
bad and not a good distance and since then she owned 25 papers using the km
然后她以公里为单位拥有25篇论文，涉及一些琐碎的一维问题
then she owned 25 papers using the km distance for some trivial 1d problems
distance for some trivial 1d problems hopefully and so lots of people
希望如此之多的人，包括我们自己，我们使用公里
hopefully and so lots of people including ourselves right we use the km
including ourselves right we use the km distance because convenient we know
距离，因为方便我们知道大家都知道这个不足
distance because convenient we know everybody knows the deficient this ok
everybody knows the deficient this ok but it's all about you know mathematical
但这全都是关于您的知识，它知道数学的简单性和确切的时间
but it's all about you know mathematical simplicity and knowing exactly when
simplicity and knowing exactly when things work and when things don't work
一切正常，当一切不正常时，您可以内部化这K个
things work and when things don't work ok so you can internalize this K of
ok so you can internalize this K of distance to what's called the family of
距离所谓的分歧家庭好
distance to what's called the family of divergence okay
divergence okay and this is the definition of this
这就是这个距离的定义，它看起来像参数
and this is the definition of this distance with parameter right it looks
distance with parameter right it looks very much different from the KL distant
与KL遥远的地区有很大的不同，所以这个问题是alpha为2减
very much different from the KL distant okay so this problem is alpha is 2 minus
okay so this problem is alpha is 2 minus R into infinity and it is obviously
R变成无穷大，当P时，它明显大于或等于0等于0
R into infinity and it is obviously greater or equal to 0 equal to 0 when P
greater or equal to 0 equal to 0 when P and Q are equal if you want to actually
如果您想真正阅读有关计算的所有信息，则Q和Q相等
and Q are equal if you want to actually read everything about calculations with
read everything about calculations with this type of alpha distances memcache is
这种类型的Alpha距离记忆快取是非常不错的报告，您可以
this type of alpha distances memcache is a very nice report okay that you can
a very nice report okay that you can download from Microsoft website with all
从Microsoft网站下载所有派生文件都在附录中，因此
download from Microsoft website with all the derivations are in the appendices so
the derivations are in the appendices so you can still have a very interesting
您仍然可以对距离K进行非常有趣的扩展
you can still have a very interesting type of extensions of the K of distance
type of extensions of the K of distance so the let me see if I need to tell you
所以让我看看我是否需要在这里告诉你什么
so the let me see if I need to tell you anything here
所以基本上我们接下来的两张幻灯片是向您展示一些限制
so basically we're having the next two slides is to show you some limiting
slides is to show you some limiting values of this alpha distances when
当Alpha将各种门移至一个时，该Alpha距离的值
values of this alpha distances when alpha takes various doors to one
alpha takes various doors to one basically what exactly you are getting
基本上您会得到什么，因此，如果您定义此系数1
basically what exactly you are getting and so if you define this coefficient 1
and so if you define this coefficient 1 plus alpha over the fewest gamma P and
加上最小的伽玛P的alpha值，当伽玛Q出现时，该系数即为
plus alpha over the fewest gamma P and this coefficient as gamma Q arise the
this coefficient as gamma Q arise the exponent of the Judis to be the Q
Judis的指数是Q分布，显然是伽马P a伽马Q
exponent of the Judis to be the Q distribution obviously gamma P a gamma Q
distribution obviously gamma P a gamma Q equal to 1 so if you take the limit at
等于1，所以当alpha达到1时，如果您在此gamez取极限，则可以
equal to 1 so if you take the limit at this gamez when alpha goes to 1 you can
this gamez when alpha goes to 1 you can see this goes to zero this goes to 1 and
看到它变成零，然后变成1，实际上你可以拿走
see this goes to zero this goes to 1 and what you can do is actually you can take
what you can do is actually you can take these powers in the definition of this
这些力量在这个阿尔法距离的定义中，并首先使用
these powers in the definition of this alpha distances and use first of all the
alpha distances and use first of all the Taylor expansions the results are
泰勒展开式，结果实际上是以前的，我不会去
Taylor expansions the results are actually previous I'm not gonna go
actually previous I'm not gonna go through everything here okay so for
可以通过这里的所有内容，例如，如果您采用分布Q
through everything here okay so for example if you take the distribution Q
example if you take the distribution Q to gamma Q you can write this as the
对于伽玛Q，您可以将其写为Q的伽玛Q对数的指数，然后
to gamma Q you can write this as the exponential of gamma Q log of Q and then
exponential of gamma Q log of Q and then you can use the turtle data since its
您可以使用海龟数据，因为它的功能在伽玛中得到了立方化，因为伽玛Q
you can use the turtle data since its function in gamma cubed because gamma Q
function in gamma cubed because gamma Q goes to 0 as alpha goes to 1 so you can
变为0，而alpha变为1，因此您可以将其写为指数为1加X
goes to 0 as alpha goes to 1 so you can write this as exponential is 1 plus X
write this as exponential is 1 plus X plus x squared over 2 so the first term
加2的x平方，所以第一个项是1加Q的伽马对数，这是
plus x squared over 2 so the first term is 1 plus gamma log of Q this is to
is 1 plus gamma log of Q this is to limit what Ricky but it's nothing major
限制Ricky的值，但可以用B减去Gamma来近似计算，这没什么大不了的
limit what Ricky but it's nothing major you can approximate this B minus gamma Q
you can approximate this B minus gamma Q P of log of P and it comes out that this
P的对数P，结果表明该积分为您提供了一种非常不错的形式
P of log of P and it comes out that this integral it gives you a very nice form
integral it gives you a very nice form that maybe some of you have seen it in
也许你们中的一些人在机器学习的不同背景下看到了它
that maybe some of you have seen it in different contexts in machine learning
different contexts in machine learning so if you take this asymptotic value and
因此，如果您采用这个渐近值，并且如果您得到的话，我们会将其插入其中
so if you take this asymptotic value and we plug them in there if you get
we plug them in there if you get basically you recover from the self of
基本上，您可以从KL Vista的距离自我中恢复
basically you recover from the self of distances the KL Vista
distances the KL Vista okay so as a matter fact when alpha we
好吧，事实上，当我们从α出发时，右边的z / 2
okay so as a matter fact when alpha we set out from goes to z/2 on right
set out from goes to z/2 on right without reverse to 1 this becomes equal
如果没有倒数为1，则等于回答您获得距离K
without reverse to 1 this becomes equal to answer you get the K of distance okay
to answer you get the K of distance okay and so this has some limiting values
所以这有一些极限值，所以当Alpha最差的一个时，您会得到
and so this has some limiting values okay so when alpha worst one you get the
okay so when alpha worst one you get the KL distance and actually here yeah so
KL距离，实际上在这里，是的，所以这是正确的，您可以得到相反的结果
KL distance and actually here yeah so this correct and you can get the reverse
this correct and you can get the reverse key and distance when alpha goes to
关键点和距离，当alpha达到负1甚至更远时，您就可以离开
key and distance when alpha goes to minus 1 in even further you can get out
minus 1 in even further you can get out of this
这甚至香农给距离，但一些
of this even the Shannon give distance but some
even the Shannon give distance but some people in network theory goes right so
网络理论的人们正确无误，因此可以通过平等对待来恢复
people in network theory goes right so this is recovered by taking after equal
this is recovered by taking after equal to 0
到0
让我看看我是否要告诉你兄弟
this is recovered by taking after equal to 0
let me see if I am going to tell you brothers
对，所以我们说好吧，让我看看我们将如何定义这个问题，所以在
right so let's say okay let me see how we're going to define this problem so in
we're going to define this problem so in everything we did like one will apply
我们所做的一切都会应用期望最大化，对吗？
everything we did like one will apply expectation maximization right do you
expectation maximization right do you remember we had a set of latent variable
记住我们有一组潜在变量Z但也有一组参数
remember we had a set of latent variable Z but also we have a set of parameters
Z but also we have a set of parameters okay and in the expectation step what we
好的，在期望步骤中，我们做了计算
okay and in the expectation step what we did is we computed the efficient
did is we computed the efficient statistics that they were effectively
他们是Z的有效期望的统计数据
statistics that they were effectively expectations with respect to the Z
expectations with respect to the Z variable for fixed parameters and then
变量以获取固定参数，然后我们就完成了足够的操作
variable for fixed parameters and then we since we completed the sufficient
we since we completed the sufficient statistics then we much mize all right
统计数据，那么我们就可以很好地合并，这样我可以做一个身体星体
statistics then we much mize all right so here can I do a body astral
so here can I do a body astral approximation what is not going to give
近似，当联合分布的时候，什么不给我
approximation what is not going to give me when the Joint Distribution of the
me when the Joint Distribution of the unknown Nathan variables Z and the
未知的Nathan变量Z和theta受精的参数具有您所需要的
unknown Nathan variables Z and the parameters theta fertilizes has what you
parameters theta fertilizes has what you see here I should have put there cure
看到这里，我应该放那里治病，看看逗号逗号，如果现在
see here I should have put there cure see that comma theta all right now if
see that comma theta all right now if you want to keep the the parameters
您想将参数theta保持为固定值，然后
you want to keep the the parameters theta to a fixed value all right and you
theta to a fixed value all right and you don't want to bother basically bistro3
基本上不想打扰成为Delta函数的bistro3，好吧，
don't want to bother basically bistro3 that becomes a delta function okay and
that becomes a delta function okay and so let's see what case this is
所以让我们看看这里考虑什么情况
so let's see what case this is considered here so the maximization of
considered here so the maximization of the lower bound is the same as the
下限与最小化qlp之间的距离相同
the lower bound is the same as the minimization of the distance between qlp
minimization of the distance between qlp so the distance between Q and P is
所以Q和P之间的距离写成减去Z的theta Q的Q
so the distance between Q and P is written minus Q of theta Q of Z this the
written minus Q of theta Q of Z this the authorization I use this is the log of
授权我使用的是联合日志的日志，可能您有ZQ theta
authorization I use this is the log of joint log likelihood you have Z Q theta
joint log likelihood you have Z Q theta just the definition okay so anyways if I
只是定义好，所以无论如何，如果我说让我们固定参数的值
just the definition okay so anyways if I say let's fix the parameters the value
say let's fix the parameters the value theta 0 expectation step all right so
theta 0期望值步骤可以正常执行，因此具有的期望值
theta 0 expectation step all right so actually does the expectations that has
actually does the expectations that has anything to do with wanna show that
想要表明正确的事情，所以我们要保留纸张
anything to do with wanna show that right so we're going to keep paper
right so we're going to keep paper tricks to 0 so the calculation that
欺骗到0，所以计算基本上涉及那里的分子
tricks to 0 so the calculation that involves basically the numerator there
involves basically the numerator there all right theta is the Delta function so
好的theta是Delta函数，所以您相信我会得到他们的帮助
all right theta is the Delta function so you believe that I'm going to get their
you believe that I'm going to get their number physique of P of Z comma theta 0
Z逗号theta的P的数字体0可以，但是基本上我们认为我们
number physique of P of Z comma theta 0 all right but basically we think that we
all right but basically we think that we don't really care because I am looking
不太在乎，因为我向下看0日期3，所以这里减去Q of
don't really care because I am looking down on 0 date 3 so out here minus Q of
down on 0 date 3 so out here minus Q of Z log of p 0 0 so minus P of Z ok some
Z log of p 0 0所以减去Z的P可以一些思考
Z log of p 0 0 so minus P of Z ok some thinking
thinking here is the join little Hydra put this
这是Hydra的小连接，这就是我们期望使用的
here is the join little Hydra put this is what we use in expectation
is what we use in expectation maximization and I like this as the
给定参数，我喜欢Z的后验
maximization and I like this as the posterior of Z given the parameters
posterior of Z given the parameters times the probability of theta 0 the
乘以theta 0的概率，基本上是theta 0的后验
times the probability of theta 0 the posterior of theta 0 basically
posterior of theta 0 basically okay so he just doesn't matter for this
好吧，所以他只是没关系，我摆脱了它，所以减去Z的Q对数
okay so he just doesn't matter for this I get rid of it so minus Q of Z log of
I get rid of it so minus Q of Z log of this divided by Q C ok and which is the
这除以QC好，这是最小化，所以我们需要最小化
this divided by Q C ok and which is the the minimization so we need to minimize
the minimization so we need to minimize K this K of distance all right
那么距离K这个距离就可以了吗？
K this K of distance all right all right so when is the minimization
all right so when is the minimization happening when Q of Z equal to P of Z
给定theta 0逗号X时，Z的Q等于Z的P时发生的情况是
happening when Q of Z equal to P of Z given theta 0 comma X this is what
given theta 0 comma X this is what actually we did from the expectation
实际上，我们是从期望步骤开始的，我们固定了所有参数
actually we did from the expectation step right we fix the parameters all
step right we fix the parameters all right and you remember what we did this
是的，您还记得我们所做的，我们计算了联接的平均值
right and you remember what we did this we computed the average of the join
we computed the average of the join locally with respect to the distribution
关于分配本地
什么是分布，然后我们平均的步长是因为
we computed the average of the join locally with respect to the distribution
what was the distribution and then step that we averaged with because the
什么是分布，然后我们平均的步长是因为
that we averaged with because the custodian of Z given the parameter ETA
给定参数ETA的Z的托管人是第一个
custodian of Z given the parameter ETA is the first
is the first she given because 0 so this step
她给出的是因为0，所以这一步实际上确实是因为它很小
she given because 0 so this step actually does come from it's the small
actually does come from it's the small part of the variational methods okay
变分方法的一部分好吧，那么你可能会问我有一个最大化
part of the variational methods okay then you may ask I have a maximization
then you may ask I have a maximization step well so so maybe now Q of Z equal
步长很好，所以也许现在Z的Q等于那个，我们要计算Q theta
step well so so maybe now Q of Z equal to that and we want to compute Q theta
to that and we want to compute Q theta shall we go back to again to the right
我们可以再回到右边吗，所以我们要记住
shall we go back to again to the right okay so we remember if this Q theta Q of
okay so we remember if this Q theta Q of Z the giant everything data and announce
Z巨人所有数据并宣布还可以，在这种情况下请记住
Z the giant everything data and announce okay and in this case remember the this
okay and in this case remember the this fixed now okay so I put cubes inside and
现在修复好了，所以我将多维数据集放进去，最新的10次就是
fixed now okay so I put cubes inside and with a latest this 10 times that is the
with a latest this 10 times that is the expectation with respect to Q of Zeta of
关于民生加入的Zeta Q的期望可以
expectation with respect to Q of Zeta of the joining of livelihood all right okay
the joining of livelihood all right okay and I have Q then I have an average with
我有Q然后我有一个关于Q theta的平均值，然后是
and I have Q then I have an average with respect to Q theta and then of the
respect to Q theta and then of the denominator basically I'm going to get
分母基本上我将得到分布theta的熵
denominator basically I'm going to get the entropy of the distribution theta
the entropy of the distribution theta and how do you find how do you update to
以及如何找到基本要最大化的theta的更新方法
and how do you find how do you update to theta you basically need to maximize
theta you basically need to maximize look at this right how are you going to
看看这个正确的，你将如何最大化这个
look at this right how are you going to maximize this
您正在验证的厚度不会过多误认为联合的可能性
you're verifying the thickness no overmuch Mises the joined up likelihood
overmuch Mises the joined up likelihood and actually yeah I was going to
实际上，是的，我当时想，他们只是在
and actually yeah I was going to thinking they're just having a
thinking they're just having a genetically Delavan theta zero for the
从遗传上讲，Delavan theta为零，假设我们必须采取更新theta
genetically Delavan theta zero for the suppose we have to take we update theta
suppose we have to take we update theta 0 here so this is their step
0在这里，所以这是他们的步骤，您只需计算
0 here so this is their step alright you only have computing the
alright you only have computing the sufficient statistics with respect to
如果我们完成有关分布多维数据集的足够统计信息
sufficient statistics with respect to the distribution cubes if we complete it
the distribution cubes if we complete it and then you maximize the joint of
然后您将关于
and then you maximize the joint of likelihood with respect to the
likelihood with respect to the parameters bottom line is you know when
参数底线是您知道何时应用此术语时
parameters bottom line is you know when you applied this term this variation
you applied this term this variation electron from the distribution that
来自分布的电子，该分布将潜在变量和
electron from the distribution that factorizes the latent variables and the
factorizes the latent variables and the parameters like that basically you
像这样的参数，基本上您会发现，因为先有一个Z
parameters like that basically you discover as you have a Z first and then
discover as you have a Z first and then you update theta you discover the E&amp;M
您更新theta，您会发现期望最大化的E＆M步骤
you update theta you discover the E&amp;M steps of the expectation maximization
steps of the expectation maximization algorithm as a matter of fact they am
实际上，他们知道我是否记得历史上的算法
algorithm as a matter of fact they am aware if I remember historically was
aware if I remember historically was developed way because people must in
发达的方式，因为人们必须在公司中使用变体
developed way because people must in have Inc have it using the variational
have Inc have it using the variational methods but now you can see sort of the
方法，但现在您可以看到TM算法的确是变种
methods but now you can see sort of the TM algorithm is really the variational
TM algorithm is really the variational approximation substance okay you missed
近似物质好了，您错过了，也许你们中的一些人还没有看到这个
approximation substance okay you missed and maybe some of you have not seen this
and maybe some of you have not seen this example but please and I think we gave
例子，但是请，我想我们给了你，我们给了他们关于这方面的功课
example but please and I think we gave you did we give them a homework on this
you did we give them a homework on this this semester all right so you have seen
这个学期没问题，所以您已经看到了，所以这是
this semester all right so you have seen it okay so this is the denoising of an
it okay so this is the denoising of an image problem well you can think of this
图像问题很好，您可以认为这是图像中的像素
image problem well you can think of this being the pixels in an image this of the
being the pixels in an image this of the noisy bodies an extra you know the
嘈杂的身体一个额外的，你知道原始的图像，但在这里，我们认为它是
noisy bodies an extra you know the original image but here we take it to be
original image but here we take it to be a binary black or white okay plus one or
二进制的黑色或白色还可以，再加上一个或减去一个就可以
a binary black or white okay plus one or minus one okay
XY的关节分布保护
the joint distributions of X Y is protects
protects times the likelihood of
乘以
Y的P给定X可以，所以我将对代数进行一些操作
protects times the likelihood of
P of Y given X okay so I am going to do some manipulation of the algebra okay
Y的P给定X可以，所以我将对代数进行一些操作
some manipulation of the algebra okay just to make things to generalize things
只是为了使事物概括化，所以我要假设的第一件事
just to make things to generalize things so the first thing I'm going to assume
so the first thing I'm going to assume the prior so we're going to compute X
先验的，所以我们要正确计算X，我们要计算
the prior so we're going to compute X right we want to compute what the
right we want to compute what the original image this if you have some
原始图像，如果您有一些嘈杂的红色监视，则为大多数网络
original image this if you have some noisy red surveillance most web
noisy red surveillance most web denoising is so the primary are X I'm
降噪是主要的X我将假设它有一个
denoising is so the primary are X I'm going to assume it will have an
going to assume it will have an exponential prominent distribution would
指数突出分布将是e减去一些能量，并且
exponential prominent distribution would be e to the minus some energy and this
be e to the minus some energy and this energy functional I write it like that
能源功能，我这样写，我记账
energy functional I write it like that where I account
where I account interactions between neighbors so this
邻居之间的互动，所以这有点像日记本，是一个嵌套模型
interactions between neighbors so this is sort of a journal is a nesting model
is sort of a journal is a nesting model okay so I put some weights between
好吧，所以我在像素I和J之间放了一些权重，但唯一的考虑因素是
okay so I put some weights between pixels I and J but the only account for
pixels I and J but the only account for this interaction science a if I and J is
如果我和J无法互动，这是我的生意，所以这是
this interaction science a if I and J is unable okay so a business my so this is
unable okay so a business my so this is a very standard way you know to
您知道的一种非常标准的方式来介绍依赖关系
a very standard way you know to introduce basically the dependencies
introduce basically the dependencies between the X pixels okay so again there
在X像素之间还可以，因此再次将区域文字用于-II
between the X pixels okay so again there is a regional writing uses into the - II
is a regional writing uses into the - II like it gives distribution and this is
像它给人分配的感觉，这就是我的精力，让我们看看
like it gives distribution and this is my energy and let's see what the
my energy and let's see what the likelihood is going to be like so the
可能性将是这样，所以可能性是其I的x的进度
likelihood is going to be like so the likelihood is a progress of x for its I
likelihood is a progress of x for its I right so it is the probability of Y
对，所以它是给定XI的Y的概率，所以您可以想到这种情况
right so it is the probability of Y given X I so you can think of this sort
given X I so you can think of this sort of being a Gaussian with some describe
是高斯人，有些描述噪音，所以我要做的就是写
of being a Gaussian with some describe noise so I'm gonna do is I'm gonna write
noise so I'm gonna do is I'm gonna write each of these terms to follow this
每个遵循此格式的术语都进入了一些能量寿命
each of these terms to follow this format is into some energy life all
format is into some energy life all right
是的，因为它是
right so because it's products of
so because it's products of Exponential's then I'm going to get the
然后，我将得到所有指数之和的期望值。
Exponential's then I'm going to get the expectation of the summation of all the
expectation of the summation of all the alarms and this allows can be Gaussian
警报，这可以使它具有一些噪声，可以是高斯式，还可以
alarms and this allows can be Gaussian right with some noise step okay all
right with some noise step okay all right
很容易
right easy
easy if I compute the joint you know if you
如果我计算出关节，您会知道您是否原谅组织或
if I compute the joint you know if you forgive the organization or the the
forgive the organization or the the posterior of X given Y I get e to the
给定YI，X的后验得到e减去能量等于能量e 0
posterior of X given Y I get e to the minus the energy equal the energy is e 0
minus the energy equal the energy is e 0 minus restoration of audiologic ok so my
减去听觉恢复还可以，所以我在巨大日志中的精力可能是这样
minus restoration of audiologic ok so my energy in my giant log likelihood this
energy in my giant log likelihood this is what we need from the variational
我们从变分方法中需要的是e到减去该能量，因此
is what we need from the variational methods is e to the minus this energy so
methods is e to the minus this energy so multinational approximation now because
现在进行跨国近似，因为这看起来很复杂，这是
multinational approximation now because this looks complicated ok in this is the
因为要简化此计算，因为我要指数
because to simplify this calculation because an exponential I am going to
because an exponential I am going to define
定义
所以我没有把米饭放到这里，但是这是你可以想到的
because an exponential I am going to define
so I do not put the rice here right but this is you can think of this is the
所以我没有把米饭放到这里，但是这是你可以想到的
this is you can think of this is the giant okay this is what it is okay so
巨人好吧，这是可以的，所以在这种液体下的巨人就这样
giant okay this is what it is okay so the giant under that liquid is so the
the giant under that liquid is so the Journal article will disconnect this
日记文章将断开此指数的连接以消失，它将
Journal article will disconnect this exponential to disappear and it will be
exponential to disappear and it will be there's a minus sign there so it will be
那里有一个负号，所以它将是XI的总和
there's a minus sign there so it will be X I times the summation over the
X I times the summation over the neighborhoods of Na VI j xj all right
Na VI j xj的街区好，再加上XI的Li这个人如此贪婪
neighborhoods of Na VI j xj all right plus Li of X I this person's so ravenous
plus Li of X I this person's so ravenous I am writing the joint of liquid but
我正在写液体的连接点，但是因为我有兴趣，只计算一下
I am writing the joint of liquid but because I'm interested only calculate
because I'm interested only calculate one factor at the time I am making the
当时我正在使包含XI的术语成为一个因素
one factor at the time I am making the terms that contain X I nothing else
terms that contain X I nothing else so there's many other terms like there
所以还有很多其他术语，例如这里x的所有邻居都是实际的
so there's many other terms like there is actual on here x all the neighbor
is actual on here x all the neighbor selector I only want to see X I because
选择器我只想看到XI，因为这实际上是我感兴趣的
selector I only want to see X I because effectively this is what I'm interested
effectively this is what I'm interested to to compute in in some iterative
以某种迭代的方式进行计算，这样陪审团将很高兴
to to compute in in some iterative manner so the jury will be happy who is
manner so the jury will be happy who is this okay so all right nice distribution
这样就可以了，好的分配是您知道最优的对数
this okay so all right nice distribution is you know that the log of the optimal
is you know that the log of the optimal right is remember it is the expectation
正确是记住，这是对治愈的期望，这还不正确
right is remember it is the expectation with the cures and here is not all right
with the cures and here is not all right so the Qi is the expectation okay of X I
所以齐是XI的期望值
so the Qi is the expectation okay of X I times this where I substance that
因为齐期望这种伪装的指数
because Qi is expectation of this disguise the exponential of the
disguise the exponential of the expectation of this and what is the
对此的期望以及XJ的期望是什么，因为二进制
expectation of this and what is the expectation of X J because the binary
expectation of X J because the binary variable
在这个琐碎的事情中，男人是如此积极
variable it's men so actively in this trivial
it's men so actively in this trivial model - you can try to access to that
模型-您可以尝试很好地获取该平均值
model - you can try to access to that average value very nice
average value very nice all right you know extremely is the
好吧，您知道的完全是完成，因此您实际上不必
all right you know extremely is the completion so you don't really have to
completion so you don't really have to calculate any sufficient statistics and
计算您只需修复XA的任何足够的统计数据和复杂的期望
calculate any sufficient statistics and complicated expectations you just fix XA
complicated expectations you just fix XA with the mean right because you need to
意思是正确的，因为您需要打破期望好吗
with the mean right because you need to break expectations okay
break expectations okay and I want you to interests right but we
我希望您的利益正确，但我们知道您在称呼“茎干”
and I want you to interests right but we are you know we're calling the stems
are you know we're calling the stems here Mui okay and we define the values
在这里，梅伊，我们定义我和我以及一个盟友的价值观-好的，我是
here Mui okay and we define the values of shall I and I plus an ally - okay I'm
of shall I and I plus an ally - okay I'm gonna finish all right so I'm going to
会没事的，所以我要回到这个例子
gonna finish all right so I'm going to come back to this example
come back to this example so maybe sakali at the end of the day
所以也许在一天结束时sakali可以使UI变得非常漂亮
so maybe sakali at the end of the day you can derive the UI to get a very nice
you can derive the UI to get a very nice cloth solution okay - solution so mr.
布解决方案好-解决方案先生就在那条线，如果
cloth solution okay - solution so mr. right around would be one line and if
right around would be one line and if you apply the mean field approximation
您以自洽的方式应用平均场逼近法很少的图像
you apply the mean field approximation in a self consistent manner few images
in a self consistent manner few images you can see you know with
你可以看到你知道与